<!doctype html>
<html>
<head>
  





<meta charset="utf-8">
<meta http-equiv="X-UA-Compatible" content="IE=edge,chrome=1">
<meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width,initial-scale=1">

<script src="https://use.typekit.net/ldp0oqv.js"></script>
<script>try{Typekit.load({ async: true });}catch(e){}</script>

<title></title>
<meta name="description" content="Fight for the Future is dedicated to protecting and expanding the Internet's transformative power in our lives by creating civic campaigns that are engaging for millions of people.">

<!-- *** social meta *** -->
<!-- facebook -->
<meta property="og:type" content="website"/>
<meta property="og:image" content=""/>
<meta property="og:image:width" content=""/>
<meta property="og:image:height" content=""/>
<meta property="og:site_name" content="Fight for the Future"/>
<meta property="og:locale" content="en_US"/>
<meta property="og:locale:alternate" content="en_GB"/>
<meta property="og:title" content=""/>
<meta property="og:description" content=""/>

<!-- twitter -->
<meta name="twitter:card" content="summary_large_image">
<meta name="twitter:site" content="fightfortheftr">
<meta name="twitter:title" content="">
<meta name="twitter:description" content=""/>
<meta name="twitter:domain" content="www.fightforthefuture.org">
<meta name="twitter:account_id" content="382376904"/>
<meta name="twittertext" content="" />

<!-- google+ -->
<meta itemprop="name" content="">
<meta itemprop="description" content="">
<meta itemprop="image" content="">
<!-- /*** social meta *** -->

<link rel="publisher" href="https://plus.google.com/102356128596404327231">

<link rel="icon" type="image/png" href="https://www.fightforthefuture.org/favicon.ico"/>

<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/css/core.css">

</head>
<body class="default ">
<header class="main-site">
  <div>
    <a href="/"><h1>Fight for the Future</h1></a>
    <button class="hamburgler" onclick="if(this.className.indexOf('focused')==-1){this.className='hamburgler focused';document.getElementById('topnav').className='visible';}else{this.className='hamburgler';document.getElementById('topnav').className='';}">Navigation</button>
    <nav id="topnav">
      <ul>
        <li><a href="/aboutus">About us</a></li>
        <li><a href="/projects">Projects</a></li>
        <li><a href="/news">News</a></li>
        <li><a href="/supporters">Supporters</a></li>
        <li><a href="https://shop.fightforthefuture.org">Shop</a></li>
      </ul>
    </nav>
    <a href="https://donate.fightforthefuture.org" class="donate">Donate</a>
    <hr/>
    <button class="share facebook">Share on Facebook</button>
    <button class="share twitter">Share on Twitter</button>
  </div>
</header>



<div class="content">
  <div class="wrap">
    <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fight for the Future</title>
    <description>Fight for the Future is dedicated to protecting and expanding the Internet&#39;s transformative power in our lives by creating civic campaigns that are engaging for millions of people.</description>
    <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.fightforthefuture.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>#SaveSecurity: digital rights group announces online campaign to oppose U.S. government attack on iPhone security</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;469&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;550&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/4a4a7c83789861261014fce6331ff82b/tumblr_inline_o44rxiqKVe1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;469&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;550&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;March 16, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;#SaveSecurity: digital rights group announces online campaign to oppose U.S. government attack on iPhone security&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future will read and display thousands of comments outside courthouse at Apple vs. FBI hearing in Riverside, CA on March 22nd &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future, the digital rights group known for organizing many of the largest Web-based protests in history, announced a new online campaign today to fight the FBI’s dangerous attempt to weaken iPhone security for millions of people. The group, which was behind nearly 50 rapid response &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-23-photos-protesters-at-apple-stores-in-40-cities/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;protests&lt;/a&gt; outside Apple stores and FBI headquarters last month, launched the site &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://savesecurity.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SaveSecurity.org&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; where they are collecting comments and signatures from concerned Internet users opposed to government backdoors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The comments will be read aloud and digitally displayed outside of the U.S. District Courthouse in Riverside, CA during Apple’s next hearing in the high profile case on Tuesday, March 22nd. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the new online campaign here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savesecurity.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://wwwSaveSecurity.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals, organizations, and companies will be able to show support for the campaign and join the online outcry against the FBI’s attack on security by changing their social media avatar or website logo to a &lt;a href=&quot;http://savesecurity.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;“lock” symbol&lt;/a&gt;, reminding the government and the public that strong security measures like encryption are saving lives every day. Tweets to the hashtag #SaveSecurity that contain comments related to the case will also be displayed and read aloud outside the courthouse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This case is not just about one phone, it’s about the future of safety and security for millions of people all over the world,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future,&lt;/b&gt; “We’ll be outside the courthouse to make sure those people’s voices are heard, because what the government is trying to do in this case doesn’t just threaten our basic rights, it puts all of us in danger. Encryption protects our hospitals, airports, and water treatment facilities. Undermining security risks lives.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protesters who gathered outside of Apple stores and FBI headquarters last month&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-23-photos-protesters-at-apple-stores-in-40-cities/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;carried&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;giant iPhone shaped banners with the message “Secure Phones Save Lives,” echoing the concerns of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2016/03/03/469091056/tech-companies-security-experts-express-support-for-apple&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;security experts&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;who largely agree that backdoors in encryption technology actually weaken national security and undermine public safety rather than strengthen it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;is best known for organizing some of the &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sopastrike.com/numbers&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;largest&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;online protests in history, including the SOPA blackout against online censorship, &lt;a href=&quot;http://resetthenet.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reset the Net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to promote encryption and fight government surveillance, and the &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;for net neutrality. The #SaveSecurity action will also rally the &lt;a href=&quot;http://internetdefenseleague.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Internet Defense League&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a network of thousands of websites that support Fight for the Future’s campaigns on an ongoing basis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future expert staff are available for interviews about the #SaveSecurity campaign and the broader implications of the Apple vs. FBI court case. Contact:&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 07:59:07 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-03-16-savesecurity-digital-rights-group-announces/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-03-16-savesecurity-digital-rights-group-announces/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Group behind nationwide Apple vs FBI protests tells Congress: backdoors in encryption make us less safe, secure phones save lives</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;683&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/254d57cbd6e22a0d27ad165d1a10d443/tumblr_inline_o3d8u2wne91ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;683&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;March 1st, 2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future issued a statement ahead of today’s Congressional hearing&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC––Ahead of today’s Congressional hearing featuring the director of the FBI and Apple’s general counsel, Fight for the Future, the group behind last week’s &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/139876985848/photos-protesters-at-apple-stores-in-40-cities&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;nationwide protests&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;at Apple stores opposing the FBI’s demand for a backdoor into the iPhone, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to Fight for the Future co-founder, Holmes Wilson:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Many members of Congress don&amp;rsquo;t understand the technical implications here, so let me put in simple terms what cybersecurity experts have been saying for years.: what the FBI is asking Apple to do will make us less safe, not more safe. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This is not a choice between privacy and national security. Backdoors in encryption put us all in danger, and make us more vulnerable to the types of attacks that the government says they’re trying to prevent.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Secure phones are saving lives every day. The engineers who maintain the IT behind airports, hospitals, power plants—they use iPhones too. If Congress makes our devices less secure by mandating backdoors, they’re putting hundreds of millions of lives at risk.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;If we allow the government to set a precedent that they can force private companies to punch holes in the technological defenses that keep us safe, it’s not a question of if someone to will exploit that to cause harm to the public, it’s a question of when. Congress needs to listen to security experts by unequivocally supporting strong encryption and opposing backdoors.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future’s grassroots rallies at Apple stores in nearly 50 cities and at FBI headquarters last Tuesday garnered international headlines and sparked considerable online conversation. Protesters carried signs reading “Don’t Break Our Phones” and “Secure Phones Save Lives,” countering the narrative that this case is only about personal privacy and working to educate decision-makers about the serious dangers posed by weakening encryption technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group, known for organizing some of the largest online protests in history, is planning another significant action opposing the FBI’s demand in the coming weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future works to defend the Internet as a free and open platform for expression and creativity, and is best known for their role organizing the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sopastrike.com%2Fnumbers&amp;amp;t=NjgyMTIxYjE4NzBjYTM1MGY1YTMwMTc3ZmUxODlhNDljOWFhZWZlMCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;massive online protests&lt;/a&gt; against SOPA, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=NGJjZmJhYWUyM2Y2MGQwMDhlMjNkODk2ZmI0MjQ3MDVmNjA2NDE3OCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; for net neutrality, and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fresetthenet.org%2F&amp;amp;t=N2FiNjMyZmU5NTQzOTJkZjY0MzY0ZTYxNWY3ZTg0ODBjMDYxOTJkZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Reset The Net&lt;/a&gt; campaign promoting encryption and online security. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or on twitter &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/fightfortheftr&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@fightfortheftr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 10:11:45 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-03-01-group-behind-nationwide-apple-vs-fbi-protests/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-03-01-group-behind-nationwide-apple-vs-fbi-protests/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS: Protesters at Apple Stores in 40+ Cities and Outside FBI HQ Push Back on Government’s Demand for Weakened iPhone Security</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;666&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;419&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/61a64768fd0c8c11bddc42807a733c48/tumblr_inline_o30yf2Wwtu1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;666&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;419&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: February 23, 2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, press@fightforthefuture.org &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christina DiPasquale, 202-716-1953 (backup number)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Protesters Carry Giant 10-foot iPhone-Shaped Banners Reading “Don’t Break Our Phones”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; View photos here:&lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WIzWH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; http://imgur.com/a/WIzWH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerned iPhone users and digital security supporters gathered at 5:30 pm local time at FBI headquarters in DC and at Apple stores in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dontbreakourphones.org/#rallies&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;nearly 50 cities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; today, Tuesday, February 23rd. Today marks one week after the Justice Department won a court order that attempts to force Apple to write software that would undermine the safety and security of hundreds of millions of people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Photos submitted from protests can be seen here:&lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WIzWH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; http://imgur.com/a/WIzWH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are rallying at Apple stores because what the FBI is demanding of Apple is going to make all of us less safe, not more safe,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future. &lt;/b&gt;“Encryption and security technology is what protects our hospitals, our airports, our water treatment facilities. If we allow the government to start forcing private companies to punch holes in these critical defenses, it’s not a question of if those backdoors will be exploited by those wishing to do harm, but when.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protesters opposed the DOJ’s demand, carrying giant&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/w5HOowY.png&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt;10-foot long iPhone banners&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;, &lt;/b&gt;and iPhone shaped signs reading “FBI: Don’t Break Our Phones” and “Secure Phones Save Lives.” Participants also turned their phones, laptops, and tablets into glowing protest signs using&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fprotestsign.org&amp;amp;t=OWI3ODkxMDllM2Q0ODIwY2U4MTgzZGY0YWM0MzAxNGI2MDEwMWU1MCxMM3JKVDZJcw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt;ProtestSign.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rallies were called for by Fight for the Future and are supported by Demand Progress, CREDO, and other advocacy organizations. Residents across the country immediately began to offer to host an event in their town and submitted the event to Fight for the Future, who provided banners and support with recruitment. Rallies were planned across the U.S. in small cities like Anchorage, Alaska, and major ones including New York, San Francisco, Washington, DC, Chicago, Los Angeles, Palo Alto, Minneapolis, Philadelphia and Boston. Outside the U.S., residents in London and Munich hosted rallies to express their concern about companies being forced to weaken encryption as a result of government pressure. This past Wednesday, San Francisco organizers hosted a rally with dozens of&lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/139516141773/photos-dozens-rally-at-apple-store-in-san&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt;San Francisco&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; r&lt;/b&gt;esidents that day on just a few hours notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map with all submitted events by independent organizers:&lt;a href=&quot;http://dontbreakourphones.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; DontBreakOurPhones.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Apple’s stand will help keep security threats at bay” said David Segal executive director of Demand Progress.  “But we will all be less safe if the FBI succeeds at its politically expedient, but shortsighted, approach.  Our devices will become more vulnerable and the sensitive data they hold will be more accessible to people who want it for malicious purposes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For interviews with Fight for the Future and Demand Progress staff members, please email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future works to defend the Internet as a free and open platform for expression and creativity, and is best known for their role organizing the&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sopastrike.com%2Fnumbers&amp;amp;t=NjgyMTIxYjE4NzBjYTM1MGY1YTMwMTc3ZmUxODlhNDljOWFhZWZlMCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; massive online protests&lt;/a&gt; against SOPA, the&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=NGJjZmJhYWUyM2Y2MGQwMDhlMjNkODk2ZmI0MjQ3MDVmNjA2NDE3OCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; for net neutrality, and the&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fresetthenet.org%2F&amp;amp;t=N2FiNjMyZmU5NTQzOTJkZjY0MzY0ZTYxNWY3ZTg0ODBjMDYxOTJkZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Reset The Net&lt;/a&gt; campaign for online security and privacy.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 18:56:13 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-23-photos-protesters-at-apple-stores-in-40-cities/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-23-photos-protesters-at-apple-stores-in-40-cities/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TODAY: Consumers Rally at 40+ Apple Stores to Protest DOJ Demand for Weakening iPhone Security Features</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Media Advisory For: February 23, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, press@fightforthefuture.org &lt;br/&gt;Christina DiPasquale, 202-716-1953 (backup number)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Protesters will Carry Giant 10-foot iPhone-Shaped Banners Reading “Don’t Break Our Phones.” In Washington, DC, Protesters will Gather at FBI Headquarters&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerned iPhone users and digital security supporters will gather at 5:30 pm local time at Apple stores in&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dontbreakourphones.org/#rallies&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; nearly 50 cities&lt;/a&gt; today, Tuesday, February 23rd, exactly one week after the Justice Department won a court order that attempts to force Apple to write software that would undermine the safety and security of millions of people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a map listing the rallies in nearly 50 cities here:&lt;a href=&quot;http://dontbreakourphones.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; DontBreakOurPhones.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT: &lt;/b&gt;Protesters will oppose the DOJ’s demand, carrying giant 10-foot long iPhone banners (&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/w5HOowY.png&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;see example&lt;/a&gt;), and iPhone shaped signs reading “FBI: Don’t Break Our Phones” and “Secure Phones Save Lives.” Participants will also be able to turn their phones, laptops, or tablets into a glowing protest sign using&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fprotestsign.org&amp;amp;t=OWI3ODkxMDllM2Q0ODIwY2U4MTgzZGY0YWM0MzAxNGI2MDEwMWU1MCxMM3JKVDZJcw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt;ProtestSign.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; The giant iPhone banners will be on hand in most of the larger cities, but not at every protest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO:&lt;/b&gt; The rallies were called for by Fight for the Future and are supported by Demand Progress, CREDO, and other advocacy organizations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rallies are being organized in a grassroots manner by individuals who agree to host an event in their town. Fight for the Future then provides those members with banners and support with recruitment. More events are being added all the time, so check back on Tuesday if you don’t see one in your area yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE: &lt;/b&gt;Rallies are already planned across the U.S. in small cities like Anchorage, Alaska, and major ones including New York, San Francisco, Chicago, Los Angeles, Palo Alto at Apple’s headquarters, Minneapolis, Philadelphia and Boston. Supporters outside the U.S. have planned rallies at Apple stores in London, and Munich. In Washington, DC, protesters&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/458361131032530/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt;will gather&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;at the FBI’s headquarters, the J. Edgar Hoover building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN:&lt;/b&gt; Tuesday, February, 23 at 5:30pm local time in each city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are rallying at Apple stores because what the FBI is demanding of Apple is going to make all of us less safe, not more safe,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future.&lt;/b&gt; “Encryption and security technology is what protects our hospitals, our airports, our water treatment facilities. If we allow the government to start forcing private companies to punch holes in these critical defenses, it’s not a question of if those backdoors will be exploited by those wishing to do harm, but when.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Apple’s stand today will help keep security threats at bay,” &lt;b&gt;said David Segal executive director of Demand Progress.&lt;/b&gt;  “But we will all be less safe if the FBI succeeds at its politically expedient, but shortsighted, approach.  Our devices will become more vulnerable and the sensitive data they hold will be more accessible to people who want it for malicious purposes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This past Wednesday, after Fight for the Future issued the call for rallies at Apple stores, there was so much interest that they decided to organize one in San Francisco that day on just a few hours notice. Dozens of people turned out to protest the FBI’s position.&lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/139516141773/photos-dozens-rally-at-apple-store-in-san&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt;See photos here.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future and Demand Progress staff members are available for interviews and can connect journalists with the hosts of rallies in specific cities upon request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future works to defend the Internet as a free and open platform for expression and creativity, and is best known for their role organizing the&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sopastrike.com%2Fnumbers&amp;amp;t=NjgyMTIxYjE4NzBjYTM1MGY1YTMwMTc3ZmUxODlhNDljOWFhZWZlMCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; massive online protests&lt;/a&gt; against SOPA, the&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=NGJjZmJhYWUyM2Y2MGQwMDhlMjNkODk2ZmI0MjQ3MDVmNjA2NDE3OCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; for net neutrality, and the&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fresetthenet.org%2F&amp;amp;t=N2FiNjMyZmU5NTQzOTJkZjY0MzY0ZTYxNWY3ZTg0ODBjMDYxOTJkZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Reset The Net&lt;/a&gt; campaign for online privacy, which was&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.theguardian.com%2Fworld%2F2014%2Fjun%2F05%2Fedward-snowden-privacy-reset-the-net&amp;amp;t=NDViYTA0YWExYzIxMmQ2MzU0NjE4MDVlMWE4YmI1MmFkNjQyNGIzZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; endorsed&lt;/a&gt; by Edward Snowden.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 08:03:06 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-23-today-consumers-rally-at-40-apple-stores-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-23-today-consumers-rally-at-40-apple-stores-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TUESDAY:  Consumers Rally at 40+ Apple Stores to Protest  DOJ Demand for Weakening iPhone Security Features</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Media Advisory For: February 23, 2016&lt;b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact:&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Christina DiPisquali, 202-716-1953 (backup number)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Protesters will Carry Giant 10-foot iPhone-Shaped Banners Reading “Don’t Break Our Phones.” In Washington, DC, Protesters will Gather at FBI Headquarters&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerned iPhone users and digital security supporters will gather at Apple stores in &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dontbreakourphones.org/#rallies&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;more than 40 cities&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;this Tuesday, February 23rd, exactly one week after the Justice Department won a court order that attempts to force Apple to write software that would undermine the safety and security of millions of people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a map listing the rallies in more than 40 cities here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dontbreakourphones.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DontBreakOurPhones.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT:&lt;/b&gt; Protesters will oppose the DOJ’s  demand carrying giant 10-foot long iPhone banners (&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/w5HOowY.png&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;see example&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), and iPhone shaped signs reading “FBI: Don’t Break Our Phones” and “Secure Phones Save Lives.” Participants will also be able to turn their phones, laptops, or tablets into a glowing protest sign using &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fprotestsign.org&amp;amp;t=OWI3ODkxMDllM2Q0ODIwY2U4MTgzZGY0YWM0MzAxNGI2MDEwMWU1MCxMM3JKVDZJcw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ProtestSign.org&lt;/a&gt;. The giant iPhone banners will be on hand in most of the larger cities, but not at every protest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO:&lt;/b&gt; The rallies were called for by Fight for the Future and are supported by Demand Progress, CREDO, and other advocacy organizations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rallies are being organized in a grassroots manner by individuals who agree to host an event in their town. Fight for the Future then provides those members with banners and support with recruitment. More events are being added all the time, so check back before Tuesday if you don’t see one in your area yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE: &lt;/b&gt;Rallies are already planned across the U.S. in small cities like Anchorage, Alaska, and major ones including New York, San Francisco, Chicago, Los Angeles, Palo Alto at Apple’s headquarters, Minneapolis, Philadelphia and Boston. Supporters outside the U.S. have planned rallies at Apple stores in Hong Kong, London, and Munich. In Washington, DC, protesters &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/458361131032530/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;will gather&lt;/a&gt; at the FBI’s headquarters, the J. Edgar Hoover building. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN:&lt;/b&gt; Tuesday, February, 23 at 5:30pm local time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are rallying at Apple stores because giving the government easier access to our data, also gives everyone else, including terrorists, thieves and stalkers, easier access to our data&amp;ndash;making all of us less safe, not more safe,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future. &lt;/b&gt;“The government’s unconstitutional attack on our digital security could put millions of people in danger, so it’s critically important that we support any fight to keep our most sensitive personal, medical, legal and financial information protected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Apple’s stand today will help keep security threats at bay” &lt;b&gt;said David Segal executive director of Demand Progress.&lt;/b&gt;  “But we will all be less safe if the FBI succeeds at its politically expedient, but shortsighted, approach.  Our devices will become more vulnerable and the sensitive data they hold will be more accessible to people who want it for malicious purposes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This past Wednesday, after Fight for the Future issued the call for rallies at Apple stores, there was so much interest that they decided to organize one in San Francisco that day on just a few hours notice. Dozens of people turned out to protest the FBI’s position. &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/139516141773/photos-dozens-rally-at-apple-store-in-san&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See photos here. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future and Demand Progress staff members are available for interviews ahead of the Tuesday rallies and can connect journalists with the hosts of rallies in specific cities upon request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future works to defend the Internet as a free and open platform for expression and creativity, and is best known for their role organizing the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sopastrike.com%2Fnumbers&amp;amp;t=NjgyMTIxYjE4NzBjYTM1MGY1YTMwMTc3ZmUxODlhNDljOWFhZWZlMCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;massive online protests&lt;/a&gt; against SOPA, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=NGJjZmJhYWUyM2Y2MGQwMDhlMjNkODk2ZmI0MjQ3MDVmNjA2NDE3OCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; for net neutrality, and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fresetthenet.org%2F&amp;amp;t=N2FiNjMyZmU5NTQzOTJkZjY0MzY0ZTYxNWY3ZTg0ODBjMDYxOTJkZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Reset The Net&lt;/a&gt; campaign for online privacy, which was &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.theguardian.com%2Fworld%2F2014%2Fjun%2F05%2Fedward-snowden-privacy-reset-the-net&amp;amp;t=NDViYTA0YWExYzIxMmQ2MzU0NjE4MDVlMWE4YmI1MmFkNjQyNGIzZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;endorsed&lt;/a&gt; by Edward Snowden.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 08:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-22-tuesday-consumers-rally-at-40-apple-stores-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-22-tuesday-consumers-rally-at-40-apple-stores-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rallies against FBI demand for iPhone backdoor planned at Apple stores in more than 30 cities this Tuesday</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1120&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;626&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/bb54d8b2c2ded7d92148d498dfa61493/tumblr_inline_o2uqogvt9t1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1120&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;626&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;February 20, 2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rallies against FBI demand for iPhone backdoor planned at Apple stores in more than 30 cities this Tuesday&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;In Washington, DC protesters will gather at FBI Headquarters&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerned iPhone users and digital security supporters will gather at Apple stores in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dontbreakourphones.org/#rallies&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;more than 30 cities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; this coming Tuesday, February 23rd, exactly one week after a court order that attempts to force Apple to write software that would undermine the safety and security of millions of people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a map listing the rallies in more than 30 cities here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dontbreakourphones.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DontBreakOurPhones.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protesters will oppose the FBI’s demand carrying giant 10 foot long iPhone banners (&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/w5HOowY.png&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;see example&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), and iPhone shaped signs reading “FBI: Don’t Break Our Phones” and “Secure Phones Save Lives.” Participants will also be able to turn their phones, laptops, or tablets into a glowing protest sign using &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://protestsign.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ProtestSign.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rallies are being organized in a grassroots manner by Fight for the Future members who agree to host an event in their town. Fight for the Future then provides those members with banners and support with recruitment. More events are being added all the time, so check back before Tuesday if you don’t see one in your area yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rallies are already planned across the U.S. in small cities like Anchorage, Alaska, and major ones including New York, San Francisco, Chicago, Los Angeles, Palo Alto at Apple’s headquarters, and Boston. Supporters outside the U.S. have planned rallies at Apple stores in Hong Kong and Munich. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Washington, DC, protesters &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/458361131032530/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;will gather&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;at the FBI’s headquarters, the J. Edgar Hoover building. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This past Wednesday, after Fight for the Future issued the call for rallies at Apple stores, there was so much interest that they decided to organize one in San Francisco that day on just a few hours notice. Dozens of people turned out to protest the FBI’s position. &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/139516141773/photos-dozens-rally-at-apple-store-in-san&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;See photos here. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are rallying at Apple stores because what the FBI is demanding here will make all of us less safe, not more safe,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“their unconstitutional attack on our digital security could put millions of people in danger, so we’re giving those people a way to get their voices heard.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future senior staff are available for interviews in advance of the Tuesday events, and can connect journalists with Fight for the Future members who are hosting these events in various cities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future works to defend the Internet as a free and open platform for expression and creativity, and is best known for their role organizing the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sopastrike.com%2Fnumbers&amp;amp;t=NjgyMTIxYjE4NzBjYTM1MGY1YTMwMTc3ZmUxODlhNDljOWFhZWZlMCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;massive online protests&lt;/a&gt; against SOPA, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=NGJjZmJhYWUyM2Y2MGQwMDhlMjNkODk2ZmI0MjQ3MDVmNjA2NDE3OCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; for net neutrality, and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fresetthenet.org%2F&amp;amp;t=N2FiNjMyZmU5NTQzOTJkZjY0MzY0ZTYxNWY3ZTg0ODBjMDYxOTJkZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Reset The Net&lt;/a&gt; campaign for online privacy, which was &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.theguardian.com%2Fworld%2F2014%2Fjun%2F05%2Fedward-snowden-privacy-reset-the-net&amp;amp;t=NDViYTA0YWExYzIxMmQ2MzU0NjE4MDVlMWE4YmI1MmFkNjQyNGIzZCw0a01wcUtXQw%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;endorsed&lt;/a&gt; by Edward Snowden.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 10:22:04 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-20-rallies-against-fbi-demand-for-iphone-backdoor/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-20-rallies-against-fbi-demand-for-iphone-backdoor/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS: Dozens rally at Apple store in San Francisco to protest FBI demand for iPhone backdoor</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;383&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/a34662c58a8e45ae03153a64ce785b4b/tumblr_inline_o2q048YFJr1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;383&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;February 17, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, CA –– Dozens of people, ranging from privacy advocates to casual iPhone users, rallied in front of Apple’s flagship store in San Fransisco this evening to protest the U.S. government’s unlawful attempt to force the company to help the FBI hack into an iPhone, which would set a dangerous precedent and threaten the safety and security of millions of iPhone users worldwide.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;See photos from the rally below. The rapid-response action was organized by digital rights group &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;. It coalesced in a matter of hours primarily on social media, and also featured speakers from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://eff.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Electronic Frontier Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is planning &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/139489301983/rallies-planned-at-apple-stores-nationwide-to&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;a large number of events&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; nationwide this coming Tuesday, a week from the date of the court order, to continue highlighting the danger posed by government mandated backdoors or weakening of encryption and security features in our devices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a list of events planned on Tuesday, Feb 23rd here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1645036165762086/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/1645036165762086/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The photos below are available for use by press:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;265&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/8a1e3801c95f89a6aed79a87131df294/tumblr_inline_o2q01dNnRb1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;265&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;428&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/78dc96f78c2253ccefaecb38e61f207c/tumblr_inline_o2q01dJErs1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;428&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;428&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/12d8dd41e698a914624064bcaadcb62b/tumblr_inline_o2q01foyps1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;428&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;383&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/a34662c58a8e45ae03153a64ce785b4b/tumblr_inline_o2q01e1NmS1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;383&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;428&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/b3869b4b178df2d39c1e489cdba803cf/tumblr_inline_o2q01fXsUP1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;428&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photos above via twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/DocPop&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/DocPop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photos below courtesy of EFF, Creative Commons-BY.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;682&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/eea81c535fc3873dd11b8a58fecdf79b/tumblr_inline_o2q9yfDr9Y1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;682&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/b4151d273f4fe46295b993a85d03f199/tumblr_inline_o2q9pfOJ591ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/2c6b382d5cb3d3a02022465bb6af95da/tumblr_inline_o2q9pnPvvB1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/bca1f7e309ae03655e86f3ab63d3c67c/tumblr_inline_o2q9pvV9o31ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 20:57:16 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-18-photos-dozens-rally-at-apple-store-in-san/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-18-photos-dozens-rally-at-apple-store-in-san/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rallies planned at Apple stores nationwide to protest court order pressuring the company to build a “backdoor” for the FBI to hack the iPhone</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;265&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://56.media.tumblr.com/8a1e3801c95f89a6aed79a87131df294/tumblr_inline_o2p9pcacnk1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;265&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;February 17, 2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Holmes Wilson, 614-465-6371, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;iPhone users will gather outside stores with a simple message for the government: “Don’t Break Our Phones.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the heels of an unprecedented &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/us-wants-apple-to-help-unlock-iphone-used-by-san-bernardino-shooter/2016/02/16/69b903ee-d4d9-11e5-9823-02b905009f99_story.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;court order&lt;/a&gt; that would require Apple to build a software “backdoor” to help the FBI break into an iPhone, digital rights group &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt; is calling for nationwide rallies outside Apple stores to demand that the U.S. government drop its dangerous request, which would &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/customer-letter/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;undermine&lt;/a&gt; the safety and security of millions of iPhone users worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The group launched a Facebook event to coordinate the protests here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1645036165762086/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/1645036165762086/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A separate website for the protests will be launched later today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;iPhone users and civil liberties supporters will rally outside Apple stores one week from the date of yesterday’s court order, at 5:30pm local time in each city on Tuesday, February 23rd. Protesters will be encouraged to bring signs, but will also have the option of loading a “Protest Sign” on their phone using Fight for the Future’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://ProtestSign.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ProtestSign.org&lt;/a&gt;, which can turn any phone, tablet, or laptop into a light-up protest sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Governments have been frothing at the mouth hoping for an opportunity to pressure companies like Apple into building backdoors into their products to enable more sweeping surveillance. It’s shameful that they’re exploiting the tragedy in San Bernardino to push that agenda,” said Evan Greer, Fight for the Future’s campaign director, “Security experts agree that any weakening or circumvention of security features on a phone puts everyone in danger. Encryption is what protects our airports, power plants, and hospitals. If the FBI succeeds in forcing Apple to help them hack into an iPhone, it will open the floodgates and set a dangerous precedent that will inevitably lead to more suffering and loss of life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protests will carry the message “Don’t Break Our Phones” and “Secure Phones Save Lives”. The FBI is asking Apple to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20160216/17393733617/no-judge-did-not-just-order-apple-to-break-encryption-san-bernardino-shooters-iphone-to-create-new-backdoor.shtml&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;write software&lt;/a&gt; that would disable one of the iPhone’s most important security features, which deletes data on the phone after 10 wrong password attempts. If they succeed in forcing Apple to do this, it would create a backdoor that could be used on all iPhones, and open massive potential for security breaches and cyber attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Facebook event for the protest was launched this morning, and will soon list specifics for events being planned in each city. The protests will happen in a 100% grassroots fashion, organized by Fight for the Future members in each city who will step up to bottomline each event. The group used similar tactics last year to organize &lt;a href=&quot;http://mashable.com/2014/11/07/net-neutrality-protest/#1p34t9NYbGq3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;widespread&lt;/a&gt; rapid response protests in support of net neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 11:27:21 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-17-rallies-planned-at-apple-stores-nationwide-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-17-rallies-planned-at-apple-stores-nationwide-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Huge win for Net Neutrality in India: new rules ban discriminatory pricing and “Zero Rating” plans like Facebook’s Free Basics</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br&gt;February 8, 2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future calls for U.S. to follow suit, ban similarly harmful practices by Comcast,Verizon, T-Mobile, and others&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, Indian telecom regulator TRAI reaffirmed the principles of net neutrality by &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/tech/tech-news/Big-win-for-net-neutrality-Telecom-regulator-prohibits-discriminatory-tariffs-for-data/articleshow/50901547.cms&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;banning&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;discriminatory pricing on the basis of content, including so called &amp;ldquo;Zero Rating&amp;rdquo; schemes like Facebook&amp;rsquo;s controversial &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/notes/access-now/open-letter-to-mark-zuckerberg-regarding-internetorg-net-neutrality-privacy-and-/935857379791271/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free Basics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; program. The decision marks a major victory for &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savetheinternet.in/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;grassroots activists&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;in India and around the world who have been calling for such a ban, and a setback for companies like T-Mobile and Verizon, who have been pushing similar practices in the U.S., claiming that they do not violate net neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 11:53:07 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-08-huge-win-for-net-neutrality-in-india-new-rules/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-08-huge-win-for-net-neutrality-in-india-new-rules/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning Releases Podcast To Tell Her Story In Her Own Words</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE:&lt;br&gt;February 5, 2015&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Actress Michelle Hendley portrays WikilLeaks whistleblower&amp;rsquo;s voice due to prison restrictions barring her from speaking directly to press&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning has released a podcast where she tells her story in her own words. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recording was produced in collaboration with Amnesty International and voiced by actress Michelle Hendley. Due to prison restrictions, Chelsea is barred from speaking to any members of the press directly, or being recorded during her incarceration, so actress Michelle Hendley (known for her performance in Boy Meets Girl) has lent her voice to Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s words for this episode of Amnesty&amp;rsquo;s series &amp;ldquo;In Their Own Words.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Find the podcast here: &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amnesty.org.uk/chelsea&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.amnesty.org.uk/chelsea&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s tweet about it here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/xychelsea/status/695553686261489664&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/xychelsea/status/695553686261489664&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 08:57:47 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-05-chelsea-manning-releases-podcast-to-tell-her-story/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-02-05-chelsea-manning-releases-podcast-to-tell-her-story/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

  </div>
</div>

<footer class="main-site">
  <div class="gutter">
    <a href="/"><img src="/img/page/homepage/logo.png"/></a>
      <div class="sharea">
        <span>Follow us:</span>
        <button class="facebook">Facebook</button>
        <button class="twitter">Twitter</button>
      </div>
    <hr/>
    <nav>
      <ul>
        <li><a href="https://donate.fightforthefuture.org"><strong>Donate</strong></a></li>
        <li><a href="/news">News</a></li>
        <li><a href="/press">Press</a></li>
        <li><a href="https://shop.fightforthefuture.org">Shop</a></li>
        <li><a href="https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/membership"><strong>Membership</strong></a></li>
        <li><a href="https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/support-us">Support Us</a></li>
        <li><a href="/projects">Projects</a></li>
        <li><a href="/supporters">Major Supporters</a></li>
        <li><a href="/jobs">Jobs</a></li>
        <li><a href="/aboutus">About Us</a></li>
        <li><a href="https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=0Bz22uTps2Ng3fjNIR3E3Mi1IQzQzSFF1V3VlemFpUlk3eEZfUlRlWDZ0MjBlcDZCMjVVTmc&usp=sharing">Financial Statements</a></li>
        <li><a href="https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/pages/buy-vpn/fftfsp"><strong>Buy a VPN</strong></a></li>
        <li><a href="/contact">Contact</a></li>
        <li><a href="/privacy">Privacy Policy</a></li>
      </ul>
    </nav>
  </div>
  <div class="dark">
    <div class="gutter">
      <p class="copyright">No copyright intended.</p>
      <p>
        For press inquiries, please call <a href="tel://15083683026">(508) 368-3026</a> or email
        <a href="mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org">press@fightforthefuture.org</a> (press inquiries only)
        <br/>
        For all other inquiries, please email <a href="mailto:team@fightforthefuture.org">team@fightforthefuture.org</a>
        |
        PO Box 55071 #95005 Boston, MA 02205
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>
</footer>

<script type="text/javascript" src="https://mothership-js.fightforthefuture.org/core.min.js"></script>
<script type="text/javascript" src="/js/core.js"></script>
<script>
  (function (i, s, o, g, r, a, m) {
    i['GoogleAnalyticsObject'] = r;
    i[r] = i[r] || function () {
        (i[r].q = i[r].q || []).push(arguments)
      }, i[r].l = 1 * new Date();
    a = s.createElement(o),
      m = s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];
    a.async = 1;
    a.src = g;
    m.parentNode.insertBefore(a, m)
  })(window, document, 'script', '//www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js', 'ga');

  ga('create', 'UA-26576645-1', 'auto');
  ga('send', 'pageview');

</script>

</body>
</html>
