<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fight for the Future</title>
    <description>Fight for the Future is dedicated to protecting and expanding the Internet's transformative power in our lives by creating civic campaigns that are engaging for millions of people.</description>
    <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.fightforthefuture.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Swamp Drains Trump: White House Signs Bill to Gut Internet Privacy</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, April 3, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bill to let ISPs collect and sell customer information has generated massive backlash from Trump supporters and progressives alike&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monday evening, President Donald Trump signed SR Res 34, a bill to slash the FCC’s Internet privacy rules and allow Internet Service Providers like Comcast, Verizon, and AT&amp;amp;T to monitor, collect, and sell the details of their customers’ Internet activity to advertisers. The legislation was passed by Congress last week, amid massive public backlash from across the political spectrum, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailydot.com/layer8/reddit-the-donald-internet-privacy-crisis/?tw=dd&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;including&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from some of Trump’s top supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future, a digital rights group that helped lead resistance to the measure, previously announced that they will &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-28-breaking-house-of-representatives-votes-to-gut/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;unleash billboards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to expose the lawmakers who voted for the measure. Today, in response to Trump signing the bill, they announced they will add a billboard specifically targeting the President.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Donald Trump said he was going to drain the swamp, but it didn’t take long for the swamp to drain him,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“the only people in the United States who want less Internet privacy are CEOs and lobbyists for giant telecom companies who want to rake in money by spying on all of us and selling the private details of our lives to marketing companies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s deeply ironic that President Trump is expressing outrage about alleged violations of his own privacy while signing legislation that will dramatically expand government surveillance of all Americans,”&lt;b&gt; she added, &lt;/b&gt;“President Trump has misjudged his base on this issue. No one wants their Internet Service Provider to sell their information without their permission.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Fight for the Future &lt;b&gt;l&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-30-following-congress-attack-on-internet-privacy/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;aunched&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/a&gt;an online resource called #GetSafe, to help Internet users protect their privacy in the wake of Congress’ attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;is best known for their role organizing the massive online protests against SOPA, the online censorship bill. and continues to organize many of the largest protests in the history of the Internet. They’ve led high profile campaigns to help win net neutrality protections, and organized the &lt;b&gt;ResetTheNet.org&lt;/b&gt; campaign against government surveillance, which was supported by hundreds of major websites and endorsed by Edward Snowden. Over the summer, they organized the high profile &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;tour featuring many celebrities and well known musicians. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;FightFortheFuture.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 20:36:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-04-04-swamp-drains-trump-white-house-signs-bill-to-gut/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-04-04-swamp-drains-trump-white-house-signs-bill-to-gut/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Following Congress’ attack on Internet privacy, Fight for the Future launches #GetSafe guide to help average internet users protect themselves online</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/5020edb3873d078d4b98edc03fddd17e/tumblr_inline_onmuknoI3H1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, March 30, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852,6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital rights group Fight for the Future has launched a new &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://letsgetsafe.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;online resource&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;called #GetSafe, a simple guide that helps average Internet users take the most important steps toward protecting the personal information stored on their phones, tablets, and computers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The release of the new tool comes on the heels of Congress voting to slash Internet privacy rules and allow Internet Service Providers to collect and sell their customer’s information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This vote in Congress is just the latest attack on our basic right to privacy and our ability to use the Internet safely,” &lt;b&gt;said Laila Abdelaziz, a campaigner at Fight for the Future,&lt;/b&gt; “many of us are already extremely vulnerable to corporate and government spying, hackers and identity thieves.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, there are simple things that everyone can and should be doing to protect themselves and their loved ones,” &lt;b&gt;she continued,&lt;/b&gt; “we launched #GetSafe to make these practices easy and accessible to everyone, regardless of how technologically savvy they are.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the #GetSafe resource here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.letsgetsafe.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tool functions like an online quiz, asking the user a series of simple questions about their digital security habits, and making basic recommendations about how to set a strong password for your phone and computer, how to switch to free encrypted text messaging services, and how to run a Virtual Private Network (VPN) to make it much harder for your Internet service provider to spy on your web browsing activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The launch of the #GetSafe tool comes as Fight for the Future is already making headlines about plans to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-28-breaking-house-of-representatives-votes-to-gut/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;unleash billboards&lt;/a&gt; listing the names of lawmakers who voted to strike down the FCC’s Internet privacy rules. The group has also launched an &lt;a href=&quot;http://savebroadbandprivacy.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;online petition&lt;/a&gt; calling for President Trump to veto the measure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt; is best known for their role organizing the massive online protests against SOPA, the Stop Online Piracy Act, and continues to organize many of the largest protests in the history of the Internet. They’ve led high profile campaigns to help win net neutrality protections, and organized the ResetTheNet.org campaign against government surveillance, which was supported by hundreds of major websites and endorsed by Edward Snowden. Over the summer, they organized the high profile &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; tour featuring many celebrities and well known musicians. Learn more at&lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FightFortheFuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 10:50:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-30-following-congress-attack-on-internet-privacy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-30-following-congress-attack-on-internet-privacy/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: House of Representatives votes to gut Internet privacy rules</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;h2&gt;Fight for the Future will unleash billboards to expose lawmakers who take large contributions from ISPs&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;2070&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1186&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/b812964cf952df044f5772ce85bc709c/tumblr_inline_onjn0cNS121ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;2070&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1186&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, March 28, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. House of Representatives just voted 215 - 205 to gut the FCC’s Internet privacy rules that prevent Internet Service Providers (ISPs) like Comcast and Verizon from selling their customer’s personal information to advertisers without their consent. The measure already passed the Senate last week, so it will now head to the President’s desk for signing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, digital rights group &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, known for organizing massive protests against SOPA and for net neutrality announced that they will put up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-27-fight-for-the-future-to-unleash-billboards-to/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;billboards&lt;/a&gt; with the names of every member of Congress who voted to sell off their constituent’s privacy rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today Congress proved once again that they care more about the wishes of the corporations that fund their campaigns than they do about the safety and security of their constituents,” said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Gutting these privacy rules won’t just allow Internet Service Providers to spy on us and sell our personal information, it will also enable more unconstitutional mass government surveillance, and fundamentally undermine our cybersecurity by making our sensitive personal information vulnerable to hackers, identity thieves, and foreign governments,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1066&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;680&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/fc0f3f4f64874df1cc4d4ca882200a2f/tumblr_inline_onjn0ux5HR1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1066&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;680&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group released a draft &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/fN5wy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;mock-up&lt;/a&gt; of what the initial billboard &amp;ndash; which will be unveiled in Washington, DC and in select districts &amp;ndash; will look like, with the names of the 50 Senators who voted for the bill last week. Today they &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/fightfortheftr/status/846758193162260481&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt; a mock-up of a billboard targeting Rep Marsha Blackburn, who has taken nearly $700,000 in contributions from telecom companies over her career. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Congress should know by now that when you come for the Internet, the Internet comes for you,” Greer added, “these billboards are just the beginning. People from across the political spectrum are outraged, and every lawmaker who votes to take away our privacy will regret it come election day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The public backlash following the party-line vote in the Senate clearly had an impact, as 15 Republicans broke ranks to vote against the controversial measure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By using the CRA to gut the FCC broadband privacy rules, lawmakers voted to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2017/03/five-creepy-things-your-isp-could-do-if-congress-repeals-fccs-privacy-protections&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;allow&lt;/a&gt; ISPs to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Monitor and sell customer’s location data, search history, app usage, and browsing habits to advertisers without your permission&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Hijack customer’s search results, redirecting their traffic to paying third parties&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Insert ads into web pages that would otherwise not have them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was instrumental in the massive grassroots campaign that successfully pushed the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) to enact the strongest net neutrality protections in US. history last year. They built the page &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com&amp;amp;t=NmRmYTc4YWQxZWM3N2UyMjYzYmNhZDZlMDFlZDQwMTY3OWY0ZGYxMSxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt;, which was responsible for more than ¼ of all the net neutrality comments received by the FCC during its feedback process, and were behind the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=N2I4ZTliYzM1MTgyYTc4NWZmOWRmMGQ1NGIyZTg3Yjc1NjA2YWQ2MixjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; protest, which was supported by more than 40,000 websites including some of the largest on the Web like Kickstarter, Etsy, Netflix, and Tumblr.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group also helped take the fight for net neutrality into the streets with creative protest campaigns like &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Foccupythefcc.com&amp;amp;t=YzVjZWM3M2Q2OGM5N2ZhZjFjMzc3ZDQ5NTE4NzExODBmMjVkMjQ1MSxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Occupy the FCC&lt;/a&gt; and the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.democracynow.org%2F2014%2F11%2F7%2Fheadlines%2Finternet_emergency_protests_across_us_condemn_latest_net_neutrality_plan&amp;amp;t=ODU4YjBmNWY5OGM4YjdlNGYxZGEyZjQyNzI1ZmNhNzg2ZDkwMWQ2MCxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Emergency&lt;/a&gt; protests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is best known for their role in the massive online protests against SOPA, the Stop Online Piracy Act, and continues to organize many of the largest protests in the history of the Internet. Over the summer, they organized the high profile &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; tour featuring many celebrities and well known musicians. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://FightFortheFuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FightFortheFuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 17:18:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-28-breaking-house-of-representatives-votes-to-gut/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-28-breaking-house-of-representatives-votes-to-gut/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>URGENT: Congress votes today on whether to gut Internet privacy. Contact the House Freedom Caucus!</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/90c106cacfadc72a81657cc523075eda/tumblr_inline_onjefdWsLc1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The House of Representatives will &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savebroadbandprivacy.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;vote today&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;on a Congressional Review Act (CRA) resolution to gut the FCC’s broadband privacy rules that prevent Internet Service Providers like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon from selling your personal information &amp;ndash; like browsing history and real-time location &amp;ndash; to advertisers without your consent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://savebroadbandprivacy.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE TO CALL YOUR REPS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rules that could be repealed also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2017/03/five-ways-cybersecurity-will-suffer-if-congress-repeals-fcc-privacy-rules&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;prevent&lt;/a&gt; ISPs from injecting ads into your web browsing, installing undetectable software on your devices to track your activity, and deploying systems to undermine encryption. When ISPs collect and store this information, they will also be making it available to the Federal government and law enforcement through bulk surveillance programs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The measure passed the Senate last week, and it was a strict party line vote with 50 members of the GOP voting to gut the rules. Given that many members of the House Freedom Caucus have taken strong previous stands for American’s right to privacy, it’s very important that we make sure they know that voters from across the spectrum want them to oppose this attack on our basic rights. Below are the names, phone numbers, and twitter handles. Please contact them now. The vote could come within hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here’s a sample script of what you can say if you call:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hi, I’m calling to ask REP NAME to protect my Internet privacy and vote against the Congressional Review Act bill coming before the House today to gut the FCC’s broadband privacy rules. Please pass my message along to the Representative. Thank you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Meadows&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;(202) 225-6401&lt;br/&gt;@RepMarkMeadows&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Amash&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-3831&lt;br/&gt;@justinamash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brian Babin&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;(202) 225-1555&lt;br/&gt;@RepBrianBabin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joe Barton&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;(202) 225-2002&lt;br/&gt;@RepJoeBarton ‏&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rod Blum&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;(202) 225-2911&lt;br/&gt;@RepRodBlum ‏&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dave Brat&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-2815&lt;br/&gt;@RepDaveBrat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jim Bridenstine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(918) 935-3222&lt;br/&gt;@RepJBridenstine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mo Brooks&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;(202) 225-4801&lt;br/&gt;@RepMoBrooks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ken Buck&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-4676&lt;br/&gt;@RepKenBuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Warren Davidson&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-6205&lt;br/&gt;@WarrenDavidson&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ron DeSantis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-2706&lt;br/&gt;@RepDeSantis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Scott DesJarlais&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-6831&lt;br/&gt;@DesJarlaisTN04&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jeff Duncan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-5435&lt;br/&gt;@RepJeffDuncan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trent Franks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-4576&lt;br/&gt;@RepTrentFranks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tom Garrett Jr.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) -225-4711&lt;br/&gt;@GarrettforVA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Louie Gohmert&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-3035&lt;br/&gt;@replouiegohmert&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Paul Gosar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-2315&lt;br/&gt;@RepGosar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Morgan Griffith&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-3861&lt;br/&gt;@RepMGriffith&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Andy Harris&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-5311&lt;br/&gt;@RepAndyHarrisMD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jody Hice&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-4101&lt;br/&gt;@CongressmanHice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jim Jordan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-2676&lt;br/&gt;@Jim_Jordan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Raúl Labrador&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-6611&lt;br/&gt;@Raul_Labrador&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Alex Mooney&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;(202) 225-2711&lt;br/&gt;@RepAlexMooney&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gary Palmer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-4921&lt;br/&gt;@USRepGaryPalmer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Steve Pearce&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-2365&lt;br/&gt;@RepStevePearce&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Scott Perry&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-5836&lt;br/&gt;@RepScottPerry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Posey&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-3671&lt;br/&gt;@congbillposey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Sanford&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;(202) 225-3176&lt;br/&gt;@RepSanfordSC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;David Schweikert&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-2190&lt;br/&gt;@RepDavid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Randy Weber&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(202) 225-2831&lt;br/&gt;@TXRandy14&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ted Yoho&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;202-225-5744&lt;br/&gt;@RepTedYoho&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 14:31:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-28-urgent-congress-votes-today-on-whether-to-gut/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-28-urgent-congress-votes-today-on-whether-to-gut/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future to unleash billboards to expose Congress members who vote to gut Internet privacy rules</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;680&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1066&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/fc0f3f4f64874df1cc4d4ca882200a2f/tumblr_inline_onhf5pOj0S1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;680&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1066&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, March 27, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;House of Representatives expected to vote tomorrow on Congressional Review Act resolution to slash FCC rules that prevent ISPs from selling customer data to advertisers&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital rights group &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, known for organizing massive protests against SOPA and for net neutrality, has announced that &amp;ndash; if the bill passes &amp;ndash; they will unleash billboards with the names of every member of Congress who votes to gut the FCC’s Internet privacy rules that prevent Internet Service Providers (ISPs) like Comcast and Verizon from selling their customer’s personal information to advertisers without their consent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group released a draft &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/fN5wy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;mock-up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; of what the initial billboard &amp;ndash; which will be unveiled in Washington, DC and in select districts &amp;ndash; will look like, with the names of the 50 Senators who voted for the bill last week. They plan to launch a crowdfunding campaign to place additional in-district billboards in key lawmakers back yards, which will also include information about how much money in campaign contributions key lawmakers took from the telecom industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Congress should know by now that when you come for the Internet, the Internet comes for you,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“these billboards are just the beginning. People from across the political spectrum are outraged, and every lawmaker who votes to take away our privacy will regret it come election day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The House of Representatives is expected to vote on the measure as soon as tomorrow. Fight for the Future is running an online campaign to stop the bill at &lt;a href=&quot;http://savebroadbandprivacy.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;SaveBroadbandPrivacy.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By using the CRA to gut the FCC broadband privacy rules, lawmakers are voting to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2017/03/five-creepy-things-your-isp-could-do-if-congress-repeals-fccs-privacy-protections&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;allow&lt;/a&gt; ISPs to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitor and sell customer’s location data, search history, app usage, and browsing habits to advertisers without your permission&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hijack customer’s search results, redirecting their traffic to paying third parties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Insert ads into web pages that would otherwise not have them&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was instrumental in the massive grassroots campaign that successfully pushed the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) to enact the strongest net neutrality protections in US. history last year. They built the page &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com&amp;amp;t=NmRmYTc4YWQxZWM3N2UyMjYzYmNhZDZlMDFlZDQwMTY3OWY0ZGYxMSxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which was responsible for more than ¼ of all the net neutrality comments received by the FCC during its feedback process, and were behind the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=N2I4ZTliYzM1MTgyYTc4NWZmOWRmMGQ1NGIyZTg3Yjc1NjA2YWQ2MixjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; protest, which was supported by more than 40,000 websites including some of the largest on the Web like Kickstarter, Etsy, Netflix, and Tumblr.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group also helped take the fight for net neutrality into the streets with creative protest campaigns like &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Foccupythefcc.com&amp;amp;t=YzVjZWM3M2Q2OGM5N2ZhZjFjMzc3ZDQ5NTE4NzExODBmMjVkMjQ1MSxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Occupy the FCC&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and the nationwide&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.democracynow.org%2F2014%2F11%2F7%2Fheadlines%2Finternet_emergency_protests_across_us_condemn_latest_net_neutrality_plan&amp;amp;t=ODU4YjBmNWY5OGM4YjdlNGYxZGEyZjQyNzI1ZmNhNzg2ZDkwMWQ2MCxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Emergency&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;protests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is best known for their role in the massive online protests against SOPA, the Stop Online Piracy Act, and continues to organize many of the largest protests in the history of the Internet. Over the summer, they organized the high profile &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour featuring many celebrities and well known musicians. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://FightFortheFuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;FightFortheFuture.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 12:30:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-27-fight-for-the-future-to-unleash-billboards-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-27-fight-for-the-future-to-unleash-billboards-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: Senate Votes to Gut Broadband Privacy Rules</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, March 23, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Statement from digital rights group Fight for the Future on Senate use of Congressional Review Act to sell Internet users’ personal information to the highest bidder&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, the U.S. Senate &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/fightfortheftr/status/844960226218590208&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;voted&lt;/a&gt; to use the Congressional Review Act to gut the FCC’s broadband privacy rules that prevent Internet Service Providers like Comcast and Verizon from selling their customer’s personal information to advertisers without permission. &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, a leading digital rights group that played an instrumental role in securing the FCC rules last year, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director, Evan Greer (pronouns: she/her):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Today, 50 members of the U.S. Senate voted to sell their constituents most personal information to the highest bidder. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;They used a blatantly undemocratic Congressional procedure to gut basic protections that prevent Internet Service Providers like Comcast and Verizon from selling their customers personal information to marketers without their permission.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;These lawmakers &amp;ndash; many of whom accept large campaign contributions from the industry groups who lobbied for this move &amp;ndash; should be ashamed that they allowed partisan politics and corporate corruption to strip Internet users of our right to use the web safely and privately. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The controversial measure passed by a narrow margin. This is evidence that many members of Congress are still scared of angering the Internet. And they should be. Internet users are increasingly aware of how legislation and FCC rules impact our basic rights, and we are prepared to fight to defend them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Senators who voted today to sell out their constituents privacy will soon learn that the money they get from Cable companies can’t buy back our trust.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;By using the CRA to gut the FCC broadband privacy rules, Senators voted to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2017/03/five-creepy-things-your-isp-could-do-if-congress-repeals-fccs-privacy-protections%20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;allow&lt;/a&gt; ISPs to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitor and sell all your location data, search history, app usage, and browsing habits to advertisers without your permission&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hijack your search results, redirecting your traffic to paying third parties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Insert ads into web pages that would otherwise not have them&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was instrumental in the massive grassroots campaign that successfully pushed the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) to enact the strongest net neutrality protections in US. history last year. They built the page &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com&amp;amp;t=NmRmYTc4YWQxZWM3N2UyMjYzYmNhZDZlMDFlZDQwMTY3OWY0ZGYxMSxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt;, which was responsible for more than ¼ of all the net neutrality comments received by the FCC during its feedback process, and were behind the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Finfographic&amp;amp;t=N2I4ZTliYzM1MTgyYTc4NWZmOWRmMGQ1NGIyZTg3Yjc1NjA2YWQ2MixjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt; protest, which was supported by more than 40,000 websites including some of the largest on the Web like Kickstarter, Etsy, Netflix, and Tumblr.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group also helped take the fight for net neutrality into the streets with creative protest campaigns like &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Foccupythefcc.com&amp;amp;t=YzVjZWM3M2Q2OGM5N2ZhZjFjMzc3ZDQ5NTE4NzExODBmMjVkMjQ1MSxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Occupy the FCC&lt;/a&gt; and the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.democracynow.org%2F2014%2F11%2F7%2Fheadlines%2Finternet_emergency_protests_across_us_condemn_latest_net_neutrality_plan&amp;amp;t=ODU4YjBmNWY5OGM4YjdlNGYxZGEyZjQyNzI1ZmNhNzg2ZDkwMWQ2MCxjUWJVeDhUcQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F142744350673%2Finternet-activists-stand-in-solidarity-with&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Emergency&lt;/a&gt; protests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is best known for their role in the massive online protests against SOPA, the Stop Online Piracy Act, and continues to organize many of the largest protests in the history of the Internet. Over the summer, they organized the high profile &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; tour featuring many celebrities and well known musicians. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://FightFortheFuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FightFortheFuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 13:26:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-23-breaking-senate-votes-to-gut-broadband-privacy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-23-breaking-senate-votes-to-gut-broadband-privacy/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Congress votes TODAY on whether to gut the FCC’s broadband privacy rules</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;480&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;481&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/d70a1980992d0288b090e5e1cde25dfa/tumblr_inline_on9xs7LiEZ1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;480&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;481&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, Thursday, March 23rd, Congress &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consumerist.com/2017/03/08/senators-officially-introduce-resolution-to-reverse-isp-privacy-rule/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;will vote&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;on whether to use a special legislative mechanism called the Congressional Review Act (CRA) to roll back the FCC’s landmark broadband privacy rules for Internet Service Providers (like AT&amp;amp;T, Comcast, and Verizon) that many of us fought hard for last year.. The 22 senators behind this controversial resolution have&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vocativ.com/411479/senators-online-privacy-money/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;received&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;more than $1.6 million from the very same companies that would profit from this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://savebroadbandprivacy.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE TO TAKE ACTION NOW!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If these privacy protections are removed, ISPs will be able to &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2017/03/five-creepy-things-your-isp-could-do-if-congress-repeals-fccs-privacy-protections&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;do the following&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitor and sell all your location data, search history, app usage, and browsing habits to advertisers without your permission&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hijack your search results, redirecting your traffic to paying third parties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Insert ads into web pages that would otherwise not have them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the full text of the resolution &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consumermediallc.files.wordpress.com/2017/03/03072017-flake-cra.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is going to be a close vote. Below are the names, numbers, and twitter handles of key members of Congress who could vote to uphold current broadband privacy rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to call them now to ask them to protect our privacy, here’s a sample script you could use:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hi, my name is ____ , I’m calling to ask Senator ____ to vote against the CRA proposal to roll back the FCC’s broadband privacy rules. Please don’t let Internet Service Providers sell my personal information without my permission.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;You can also tweet at your representatives, something like:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dear @RepTwitterHandle please protect #BroadbandPrivacy. Don’t let ISPs sell my personal information.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the key lawmakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Lisa Murkowski * (202) 224-6665 * @lisamurkowski&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Susan Collins * (202) 224-2523 * @SenatorCollins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Jerry Moran * (202) 224-6521 * @JerryMoran&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Cory Gardner * (202) 224-5941 * @SenCoryGardner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Benjamin Sasse * (202) 224-4224 * @BenSasse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Dean Heller * (202) 224-6244 * @SenDeanHeller&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 11:33:17 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-23-congress-votes-today-on-whether-to-gut-the-fccs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-23-congress-votes-today-on-whether-to-gut-the-fccs/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Outreach materials to help your community #GetSafe</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future has launched &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;#GetSafe&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a new online resource that makes it easy for everyone to take the first steps toward protecting the sensitive information stored on their phones and computers. In this post are outreach materials that advocacy organizations, school leaders, communities of faith, and others can use to help get this important information to their members.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to tailor these to make them more relevant to your audience. If you create new graphics that other groups can use or have great ideas, let us know: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:team@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;team@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sample Tweets&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copy and paste these tweets to help spread the word. Add hashtags relevant to your community. You can attach some of the graphics below to your tweet as well.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;No more excuses. Take these 6 simple steps to protect your phone &amp;amp; computer from stalkers, thieves &amp;amp; cops: letsgetsafe.org #GetSafe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump is targeting immigrants, activists &amp;amp; communities of color with surveillance. Time to defend ourselves LetsGetSafe.org #GetSafe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protecting your personal information on your phone and computer can feel overwhelming. This makes it easy: letsgetsafe.org #GetSafe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re not taking these simple steps to secure your phone &amp;amp; computer, you could be putting your friends in danger letsgetsafe.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joining #TheResistance to fight injustice? Make sure your friends and family #GetSafe and protect themselves at letsgetsafe.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You lock your door when you leave your home, but do you lock your phone &amp;amp; laptop too? Visit letsgetsafe.org to #GetSafe online!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t be the reason someone’s nude pictures leak. Lock down your phone and #GetSafe online: letsgetsafe.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The security of your DMs, photos, texts, banking info, browsing history, &amp;amp; real-time location could all be at risk. LetsGetSafe.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sample Graphics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Use these images for use on Facebook, Instagram, your blog, and other social media channels. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/NqqIi&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; for a gallery with the full size versions, and then right click to download. Be sure to include a link to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/94798eee58e61e5373ec4c9bf7746202/tumblr_inline_omyrppJwFu1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/5020edb3873d078d4b98edc03fddd17e/tumblr_inline_omyror0xtK1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/9b494680d56aed7292f06558cf337c3d/tumblr_inline_omz7efGUk71up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/4dc41b59b7a3164c05624d242cb1326d/tumblr_inline_omyrqscSom1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/4e812ae47a28c5353d5058c8aab3da4d/tumblr_inline_omyrt25C4L1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/51c044d8bdf98181ada7f73dc554bb73/tumblr_inline_omz7ewP0WB1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/256951e064385dc1f1e246cf366a8e95/tumblr_inline_omz7fev2Fh1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/7e8a4eae02e6dbe46b073a0176822ccc/tumblr_inline_omyrtluHc31ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/34958f233108a9bd7005bb37f5c193bf/tumblr_inline_omz7gieSxf1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/1521b16ba2437dd5c5dee762c25801a5/tumblr_inline_omz7hcpbTj1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/6a77e15400384a802ae13e26cffda7b4/tumblr_inline_omz7i4doVF1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/20dcd8e82a87a054dc67bfe69fb36167/tumblr_inline_omyrvwg5dF1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/ff3a8ca77557ee3e22c7b71ee96a30bb/tumblr_inline_omz7ihRmg51up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/4b2b5e08a3655aaaca35b2e533c9fa05/tumblr_inline_omyrzphux21ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/9c0bd0fe473b03f8240c182b4c3f6429/tumblr_inline_omz95maSqb1up8o7g_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;940&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;788&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/a734fe04a6bad4e28a53235952a1e4e6/tumblr_inline_omz7jvJylg1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;940&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;788&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;541&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/5d4a1d73b8fdcd4c77712690ef30c100/tumblr_inline_omyryenqdK1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;541&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;318&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/3d067b5a784f11fb174bc194d8a75f1a/tumblr_inline_omyru5JlxY1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;318&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sample Email&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Here’s a sample email text that you can send to your members. Add some information that makes it relevant to them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protecting your personal information on your phone and computer can feel overwhelming, but it’s necessary to keep yourself, your family, and your community safe. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;That’s why our friends at Fight for the Future developed an easy-to-use guide to help anyone take their first steps towards digital security. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s called #GetSafe, and it makes it easy to start protecting yourself from identity thieves, stalkers, and intrusive government surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The more people who take these basic steps, the safer we’ll all be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;letsgetsafe.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to see how easy it is to start protecting your phone and computer today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;br/&gt;-YOUR NAME&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sample Blog Post&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Here’s a sample blog post that you can use on your website or Tumblr. Be sure to adapt it to explain to your members why they should particularly be concerned about their digital security, and include one of the images above..&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this day and age, everyone needs to be thinking about protecting the information stored on our phones and computers. Our most personal information: private messages, credit card numbers, real-time location, home address, can be easily stolen by identity thieves or stalkers, or monitored by law enforcement or immigration officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protecting yourself online can feel overwhelming, but our friends at &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt; have built a new tool that makes it easy, even for those who us who struggle with technology!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s called #GetSafe. Check it out here and learn what steps you can take to protect yourself and your family: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Encryption may sound complicated, but the reality is that there are simple and important ways that all of us can protect ourselves that make it much much harder for our private information to fall into the wrong hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know that the government &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/jennifergranick/2013/08/14/nsa-dea-irs-lie-about-fact-that-americans-are-routinely-spied-on-by-our-government-time-for-a-special-prosecutor-2/#394a97a99e8c&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;routinely&lt;/a&gt; scans our digital communications without a warrant and many companies &lt;a href=&quot;https://thestack.com/security/2015/08/24/how-corporate-data-brokers-sell-your-life-and-why-you-should-be-concerned/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sell&lt;/a&gt;  their customer’s information, online activity, and purchasing habits for profit. Identity theft is on the rise, and can be costly and time consuming if it happens to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, there are a few basic things that all of us can be doing right now to #GetSafe, and the more of us who take these steps, the safer we all are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.letsgetsafe.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;letsgetsafe.org&lt;/a&gt; today to take the first steps towards digital safety and security!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 10:53:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-17-outreach-materials-to-help-your-community-getsafe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-03-17-outreach-materials-to-help-your-community-getsafe/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future statement regarding withdrawal from the Trans-Pacific Partnership agreement</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/3b2d5572272d5869ae73bccb405eb90c/tumblr_inline_ok8ne8lwMo1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, January 23, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/23/politics/trans-pacific-partnership-trade-deal-withdrawal-trumps-first-executive-action-monday-sources-say/index.html?adkey=bn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;reporting&lt;/a&gt; that Donald Trump’s first executive action will be to withdraw from the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement. It’s important for the public to understand the context of how the TPP was defeated. By the time the deal came up for a vote in Congress late last year, all the leading Presidential candidates opposed it, due to widespread opposition from across the political spectrum, sparked by a grassroots, years-long, international movement. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/nov/28/tpp-protests-mass-opposition-worked-trump-presidency&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;piece&lt;/a&gt; in The Guardian chronicles some of that history.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future, the digital rights group who organized many of the largest protests against the TPP in the United States, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director, Evan Greer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The victory against the TPP belongs to the people, not to Donald Trump or any other politician. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unprecedented international movement of people and organizations from across the political spectrum came together, and lead nothing short of an uprising that stopped an outright corporate takeover of our democratic process. Together we sounded the alarm, and made the TPP so politically toxic that no presidential candidate who wanted to be elected could support it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP would have lead to widespread Internet censorship, undermined human rights, and devastated our economy and the planet. Corporations attempted to turn the deal into a wishlist for policies they knew they could not pass through a more transparent process. But an unlikely band of labor unions and tech companies, environmentalists, hackers, and Tea Party patriots took on the world’s largest and most powerful corporations, and we won.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we enter a new stage in history, let the movement that stopped the TPP serve as a reminder to the incoming administration: we the people are organized and powerful. We will not tolerate attacks on our basic rights, whether they come from corporations or the government. If you come for our freedom, we will fight you and we will win.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future has been instrumental in the movement against the TPP. They spearheaded the coalition behind &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fstopfasttrack.com&amp;amp;t=YmI5MGJhNDBiZmU4ZjE4NWY3MjliYTZiYjcxOGZhY2ZjNmVjM2RiNCxBQXNqbVdRZg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F153056628623%2Ffight-for-the-future-statement-on-the-death-of-the&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;StopFastTrack.com&lt;/a&gt; that drove hundreds of thousands of emails and phone calls to Congress in opposition to Trade Promotion Authority legislation needed to pass the TPP, and organized creative stunts like&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DWDKzwB8GhN0&amp;amp;t=MTk4OTRiZGNjMWU4NWVhY2Q3ZTkxMmZkMGZkZGE3Y2YzMjQ5NzFlNSxBQXNqbVdRZg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F153056628623%2Ffight-for-the-future-statement-on-the-death-of-the&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; flying blimps&lt;/a&gt; outside of fence-sitting Congress member’s offices. They organized thousands of websites for an online &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/117173257703/thousands-of-websites-protest-fast-track-trade&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;“Internet Vote”&lt;/a&gt; protest against the TPP, and sent &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/121088291048/photos-video-house-republicans-receive&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;“rubber stamps”&lt;/a&gt; to Republicans who were considering supporting Obama’s trade deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most recently, the group lead the largest ground mobilizations against the TPP to date on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Frockagainstthetpp.org&amp;amp;t=YjMyNzMzYzNmMWVhNDYwZWQ5Mzc0YjlkZDIwOTdhNTU0MGJiMDE0ZCxBQXNqbVdRZg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F153056628623%2Ffight-for-the-future-statement-on-the-death-of-the&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; concert tour, which featured an array of well known musicians and celebrities including Rage Against the Machine guitarist Tom Morello, actress Evangeline Lilly, hip hop icon Talib Kweli, comedian Hari Kondabolu, and punk legends Anti-Flag, and Jello Biafra of the Dead Kennedys. The tour drew large crowds across the country and helped opposition to the TPP reach into the cultural mainstream, with high profile media coverage and a large multigenerational following.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for Future is best known for organizing the massive online protests against the SOPA internet censorship bill in 2012, and has since won major victories for net neutrality and against government surveillance. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fightforthefuture.org&amp;amp;t=MTg0NWY2OWM3NTM0Yzk5NTZlMjEyNzVkYjI0MGQwMDZlN2I0NzI4ZCxBQXNqbVdRZg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F153056628623%2Ffight-for-the-future-statement-on-the-death-of-the&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 10:09:15 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-23-fight-for-the-future-statement-regarding/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-23-fight-for-the-future-statement-regarding/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning sentence commuted following massive public outcry from across the political spectrum</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, January 17, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White House just announced that President Obama has commuted the majority of imprisoned whistleblower Chelsea Manning’s sentence 35 year sentence. She will be released on May 17th, 2017 having already served more than 6 years, longer than any other whistleblower in U.S. history.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, who has been an ardent supporter of Chelsea’s and speaks to her on the phone on a regular basis, released the following statement:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chelsea’s release is massive victory for free speech, human rights, and democracy. As someone who has become friends with Chelsea over the last year, but has never had a chance to see her face or give her a hug, I&amp;rsquo;m overjoyed that she will be able to share her beautiful self with the world. She has so much to offer, and her freedom will be a testament to the power of grassroots organizing. I’m so excited for the world to get to know her as the compassionate, intelligent, and kind person who she is.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 100,000 people signed an official &lt;a href=&quot;https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/commute-chelsea-mannings-sentence-time-served-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Whitehouse.gov petition&lt;/a&gt;, meeting the threshold to require a response from the President.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of thousands have &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/148748864883/photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-more&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;signed&lt;/a&gt; previous &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/126992085883/photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-100000&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;petitions&lt;/a&gt; organized by Fight for the Future and other groups decrying Chelsea’s treatment while in prison&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ACLU and more than a dozen prominent LGBT organizations &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclu.org/news/aclu-and-lgbt-groups-call-obama-grant-clemency-chelsea-manning&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama calling for Chelsea’s commutation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amnesty International &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freechelsea.com/amnesty-international/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama, and supporters &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amnesty.org.uk/actions/obama-free-chelsea-manning-now&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent over 25,000 emails&lt;/a&gt; to the White House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights Watch &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hrw.org/news/2017/01/13/letter-president-obama-support-commutation-chelsea-mannings-sentence&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama supporting clemency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of other human rights, free speech, government transparency, and civil liberties organizations have called for Chelsea’s release&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wide range of notable people have publicly supported Chelsea including Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg, retired U.S. Air Force Colonel Morris C. Davis, journalist Glenn Greenwald, Sean Ono Lennon, REM lead singer Michael Stipe, comedian Margaret Cho, Thurston Moore, Tom Morello of Rage Against the Machine,, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://freechelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FreeChelsea.com&lt;/a&gt;, and follow Chelsea on Twitter at &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/xychelsea&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@xychelsea&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 17:48:19 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-17-chelsea-manning-sentence-commuted-following/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-17-chelsea-manning-sentence-commuted-following/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Internet Wants to Give Chelsea Manning A Hug</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;899&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;691&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/49e8f177a41a06f2357a4b6052d6e407/tumblr_inline_ojvip3MmrV1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;899&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;691&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, January 16, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thousands are joining online #HugsForChelsea campaign, posting photos with arms outstretched calling for President Obama to grant commutation request&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/155717758898/chelsea-manning-reportedly-on-president-obamas&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; that Chelsea Manning is on President Obama’s “short list” for a possible commutation, the Internet has exploded with support for the imprisoned transgender transparency advocate. Over the weekend, thousands of people started taking part in a spontaneous &lt;a href=&quot;http://hugsforchelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;#HugsForChelsea&lt;/a&gt; campaign, posting photos of themselves with their arms outstretched as if waiting to give Chelsea Manning a hug, calling for President Obama to grant her clemency. Some prominent individuals including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/dustinkensrue/status/820436190092558336&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Michael Stipe&lt;/a&gt; of REM have joined the effort. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a selection of #HugsForChelsea photos here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/GS2Tw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/GS2Tw&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the landing page for the campaign &lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/petitions/hugsforchelsea-give-chelsea-manning-a-hug/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chelsea has so much love and support coming from people across the political spectrum,” said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, who posted the first #HugsForChelsea photo, “She has suffered enough. People are coming out of the woodwork to speak out. President Obama needs to do the right thing and free her now. After getting to know her as one of her supporters over the last year, I personally can’t wait to give her a hug.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As President Obama’s days in office wind down, people from all walks of life are standing in solidarity with Chelsea and urging the President to save her before it is too late,” said Chase Strangio, Chelsea’s ACLU attorney. “After years of suffering in prison under horrific conditions including long stretches of solitary confinement, the denial of health care for gender dysphoria and arbitrary punishments including for attempting suicide, Chelsea needs to be set free before this treatment results in her death.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More than 100,000 people signed an official &lt;a href=&quot;https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/commute-chelsea-mannings-sentence-time-served-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Whitehouse.gov petition&lt;/a&gt;, meeting the threshold to require a response from the President.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of thousands have &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/148748864883/photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-more&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;signed&lt;/a&gt; previous &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/126992085883/photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-100000&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;petitions&lt;/a&gt; organized by Fight for the Future and other groups decrying Chelsea’s treatment while in prison&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ACLU and more than a dozen prominent LGBT organizations &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclu.org/news/aclu-and-lgbt-groups-call-obama-grant-clemency-chelsea-manning&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama calling for Chelsea’s commutation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amnesty International &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freechelsea.com/amnesty-international/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama, and supporters &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amnesty.org.uk/actions/obama-free-chelsea-manning-now&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent over 25,000 emails&lt;/a&gt; to the White House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights Watch &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hrw.org/news/2017/01/13/letter-president-obama-support-commutation-chelsea-mannings-sentence&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama supporting clemency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of other human rights, free speech, government transparency, and civil liberties organizations have called for Chelsea’s release&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wide range of notable people have publicly supported Chelsea including Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg, retired U.S. Air Force Colonel Morris C. Davis, journalist Glenn Greenwald, Sean Ono Lennon, REM lead singer Michael Stipe, comedian Margaret Cho, Thurston Moore, Tom Morello of Rage Against the Machine,, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://freechelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FreeChelsea.com&lt;/a&gt;, and follow Chelsea on Twitter at &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/xychelsea&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@xychelsea&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 07:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-16-the-internet-wants-to-give-chelsea-manning-a-hug/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-16-the-internet-wants-to-give-chelsea-manning-a-hug/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boston Police scrap plan to purchase social media surveillance software following public backlash over civil liberties</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;788&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;940&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/03fba96c6d8c3a5faa3b53865acb0ef4/tumblr_inline_ojrveocXKF1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;788&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;940&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, January 14, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Boston Police Department &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2017/01/14/boston-police-scrap-plans-buy-social-media-monitoring-software-for-now/rIzAn4e5oQJJSwM4BSkt5H/story.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; yesterday that &amp;ndash; for now &amp;ndash; they will not be moving ahead with their plan to spend $1.4 million on social media monitoring software. The announcement comes amid growing public outcry about the plan, which would have given local police Orwellian capabilities to constantly scan and analyze online speech in the area.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a huge victory and offers a glimmer of hope for our basic rights at a time when it is in short supply,” said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, a group that led efforts to oppose the BPD’s surveillance aspirations, “Mass surveillance programs like the one the Boston Police intended to launch don’t actually make us safer, but they have a profoundly chilling effect on freedom of speech and our basic civil rights.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, digital rights group Fight for the Future and a dozen other civil liberties organizations &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wbur.org/news/2016/12/13/boston-police-social-media-monitoring-opposition&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to the mayor and city council calling for them to halt the plan. In coordination with the Massachusetts chapter of the ACLU, they also collected thousands of signatures on &lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/petitions/boston-police-want-14-million-to-buy-social-media-monitoring-software-2&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a petition&lt;/a&gt; from Bostonians opposed to the deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the Boston Globe issued a misguided endorsement of the BPD plan, Greer wrote &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/58480bf6e4b0ca53e4b9c1ec?timestamp=1481117010651&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a rebuttal&lt;/a&gt;, which was widely shared. BPD drew even &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bostonglobe.com/opinion/letters/2017/01/05/boston-police-should-blocked-from-buying-new-surveillance-tools/ssyPDkqPBpUsZSb39MY2IK/story.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;more criticism&lt;/a&gt; on the plan when it was revealed that they had bent the rules in the Boston Trust Act in order to hand over at least 9 people to federal immigration officials for deportation, violating a city policy preventing cops from getting involved in immigration enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“City governments and law enforcement agencies around the country should take note of what happened here in Boston. The public will not allow them to waste our tax dollars on dangerous tools that won’t make us safer but will enable mass discrimination and violations of our rights,” Greer added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future is a digital rights nonprofit best known for organizing the largest online protests in history against SOPA, for net neutrality, and against government surveillance. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://FightForTheFuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FightForTheFuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or follow us on Twitter at &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/fightfortheftr&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@fightfortheftr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 08:42:33 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-14-boston-police-scrap-plan-to-purchase-social-media/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-14-boston-police-scrap-plan-to-purchase-social-media/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning reportedly on President Obama’s “short list” for Commutation</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, January 11, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Hundreds of thousands of petition signers, dozens of LGBTQ and human rights organizations have condemned U.S. government’s treatment of Chelsea, called for her release&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;NBC News is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/army-leaker-chelsea-manning-obama-s-short-list-commutation-n705441&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;reporting&lt;/a&gt; that Chelsea Manning, who has served 7 years of a 35 year sentence, is on President Obama’s “short list” for commutation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chelsea Manning’s attorney at the ACLU, Chase Strangio, said:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Obama administration has done many commendable things to protect the rights of LGBTQ people, but in the case of Chelsea Manning they have systematically mistreated her and denied her access to medically recommended gender-related health care. Chelsea won’t survive another 5 years in prison, much less another 30. President Obama has 9 days to do the right thing and commute her sentence. The world is watching, and we hope that he stands on the side of justice, and that his legacy will be one of standing up for trans people’s rights, not having extinguished one of our community’s brightest lights.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chelsea’s Appellate Counsels Nancy Hollander and Vincent Ward said:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s appellate counsel we urge President Obama to act now and commute her sentence to time served. Her appeal will take years. It is past time to start caring for a Soldier who stood up for all of us.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, said:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chelsea Manning is a compassionate, thoughtful, brilliant human being whose actions have always been motivated by the same thing: her desire to help people and make the world a better place. She has suffered enough. President Obama should act now to right this wrong before it’s too late.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/army-leaker-chelsea-manning-obama-s-short-list-commutation-n705441&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NBC News report&lt;/a&gt; is accurate and President Obama moves to commute Manning’s sentence, he will be responding to overwhelming public outcry about Chelsea’s mistreatment while incarcerated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-More than 100,000 people signed an official &lt;a href=&quot;https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/commute-chelsea-mannings-sentence-time-served-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Whitehouse.gov petition&lt;/a&gt;, meeting the threshold to require a response from the President.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Hundreds of thousands have &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/148748864883/photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-more&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;signed&lt;/a&gt; previous &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/126992085883/photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-100000&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;petitions&lt;/a&gt; organized by Fight for the Future and other groups decrying Chelsea’s treatment while in prison&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-The ACLU and more than a dozen prominent LGBT organizations &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclu.org/news/aclu-and-lgbt-groups-call-obama-grant-clemency-chelsea-manning&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama calling for Chelsea’s commutation&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Amnesty International &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freechelsea.com/amnesty-international/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; to President Obama, and supporters &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amnesty.org.uk/actions/obama-free-chelsea-manning-now&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent over 25,000 emails&lt;/a&gt; to the White House&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Dozens of other human rights, free speech, government transparency, and civil liberties organizations have called for Chelsea’s release&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-A wide range of notable people have publicly supported Chelsea including Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg, retired U.S. Air Force Colonel Morris C. Davis, journalist Glenn Greenwald, Sean Ono Lennon, REM lead singer Michael Stipe, comedian Margaret Cho, Thurston Moore, Tom Morello of Rage Against the Machine,, and many others.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://freechelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FreeChelsea.com&lt;/a&gt;, and follow Chelsea on Twitter at &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/xychelsea&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@xychelsea&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 08:55:46 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-11-chelsea-manning-reportedly-on-president-obamas/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-01-11-chelsea-manning-reportedly-on-president-obamas/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future stands with Standing Rock</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/c1d5746e8403864c0cddd8b5b9784787/tumblr_inline_ohoimeBSQF1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This post was written by Lilia Villa, a former FFTF campaigner who is currently at Standing Rock. Photos by Lilia Villa as well.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We call on all Internet users to educate themselves, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ocetisakowincamp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; and help spread the word about what is happening in North Dakota at the Standing Rock Indian Reservation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Native Americans who are speaking out have been brutally attacked and placed under extreme surveillance by the U.S. government. Most recently a young woman was severely injured and may lose her arm after police fired concussion grenades into a crowd. [1] We fight to defend the Internet for exactly these moments&amp;ndash;when human rights are being trampled and the world needs to pay attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Army Corps of Engineers &lt;a href=&quot;http://bismarcktribune.com/news/state-and-regional/people-delivering-supplies-to-protest-camp-could-get-fine/article_9b017156-f1c2-5f02-9261-d2821c1fdfbe.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;has issued&lt;/a&gt; an eviction notice to the Standing Rock water protectors, claiming they will not have permission to camp there after December 5th. A spokesperson for the Morton County Sheriff’s department has said that if they stay, &amp;ldquo;they have to live with the consequences of potentially freezing to death.&amp;rdquo; They have also warned that those delivering supplies could face up to a $1k fine. We can only assume the human rights situation will worsen if the government moves ahead with this plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you read this, Dakota Access Pipeline, LLC, is knowingly plowing through sacred sites, burial grounds, and preparing to drill under the river without a permit &amp;ndash; threatening the water supply of nearly 18 million Americans and the nation’s largest aquifer [2] &amp;ndash; all with what appears to be full support from both state and federal authorities.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Water Protectors, as the #NoDAPL movement has asked to be called, continue to be brutalized with excessive militarized force while praying peacefully in opposition.[3] Major news networks have failed to cover the story on television, making social media instrumental in helping indigenous people share the continued oppression and human rights violations as they play out in real time on Facebook Live - feeding the growing resistance in solidarity that’s now become an international movement.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/2eb44b7e7aa5f602fd33d62a8e483eed/tumblr_inline_ohoip1P0cM1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a big deal. Over 300 indigenous tribes from across the US and around the world have converged along with thousands of allies for what many have called “the largest, most diverse tribal action in at least a century, perhaps since Little Bighorn.” [4] &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While technology has helped them tell their story and find support, even more powerful people and institutions are using technology to conduct indiscriminate surveillance and suppression of free speech. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may have noticed your Facebook timeline erupting with what seemed like friends traveling and “checking in” to the Standing Rock Reservation in North Dakota in the last few weeks. According to a viral post, the flood of check-ins was intended to “overwhelm and confuse” police agencies, saying that the Morton County Sheriff’s Department had been using check-ins to identify and “target” water protectors. [5]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/90efeb8f5992c33cb5c78c1f962bda80/tumblr_inline_ohoipmAM7e1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Law enforcement and private DAPL security have maced, tear gassed, shot rubber bullets, exploded CS (tear gas) grenades, sprayed water cannons in sub-zero temperatures, and released attack dogs on water protectors. They have arrested hundreds so far, targeting indigenous people and leaders, and even caged some in dog kennels [6]&amp;ndash; all for praying to defend their land and their drinking water. Both the UN and Amnesty International are now monitoring the human rights abuses happening at Standing Rock as public outrage keeps growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With more than 1.5 million check-ins, it was probably the largest counter-surveillance action ever taken. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putting aside the effectiveness of it, the Facebook users that checked in at Standing Rock water protector camps believed they were creating cover for activists who were actually there, and whose social media presence was being monitored by law enforcement. That means over 1.5 million people worked together to protect indigenous people, and to evade the ubiquitous surveillance of our social networks by law enforcement. That is huge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;4032&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2268&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/0bf1b42e4b35f9ed4b707e8341979807/tumblr_inline_ohoipyQ4sB1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4032&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2268&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But law enforcement has been doing more than just following social media posts. Signs of illegal &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IMSI-catcher&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;IMSI catcher&lt;/a&gt; intrusion, or &amp;ldquo;stingrays,&amp;rdquo; and other surveillance tactics have been reported on the ground. Cell phone communications and video live feeds have been disrupted, often at critical times when law enforcement attacks on the water protectors are most intense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People have reported having their phones misbehaving in odd ways. Batteries dying without warning are the most common reports. But there are creepier incidence, like FaceTime turning on by itself, voice recorders activating, apps malfunctioning, browsers seizing, messages disappearing, and strange noises during calls. My iPhone reset itself as if brand new from the box in my first week at Standing Rock.&amp;ldquo; [7]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 20, the National Lawyers Guild (NLG) and the ACLU submitted FOIA and Open Records Requests to investigate the possible use of unconstitutional surveillance at Standing Rock. [8] In the press release, they noted that “Water Protectors and allies have been continuously surveilled by low-flying planes, helicopters, and drones, and have had local cell phone communications jammed and possibly recorded.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is happening at Standing Rock is an unprecedented crisis, and we are all witness to it. It is inexcusable to have, on American soil, a racist policy being enforced with police brutality, censorship, human rights abuses, and to have silence from our elected officials in response. Also, climate change is real, it threatens all of us, and actions to slow and stop fossil fuel infrastructure—while the world transitions to solar energy—are the front lines of the fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/e0518920adf1d7af956c9066271ea7d5/tumblr_inline_ohoiqkL4DD1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5184&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;We stand in solidarity with the water protectors at Standing Rock and ask anyone who wants to support their efforts to visit the websites for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ocetisakowincamp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oceti Sakowin Camp&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sacredstonecamp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Sacred Stone Camp&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://medichealercouncil.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Standing Rock Medic + Healer Council&lt;/a&gt; to get involved in their efforts. You can help by going there to join them &amp;ndash; and if you can’t &amp;ndash; by getting loud in your communities and donating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spread the word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;lt;3 Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sources:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/nov/22/dakota-access-pipeline-protester-seriously-hurt-during-police-standoff-standing-rock&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/nov/22/dakota-access-pipeline-protester-seriously-hurt-during-police-standoff-standing-rock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sfweekly.com/news/news-news/standing-standing-rock/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.sfweekly.com/news/news-news/standing-standing-rock/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.democracynow.org/2016/11/21/headlines/standing_rock_100_injured_after_police_attack_with_water_cannons_rubber_bullets_mace&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.democracynow.org/2016/11/21/headlines/standing_rock_100_injured_after_police_attack_with_water_cannons_rubber_bullets_mace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/09/12/us/12tribes.html?_r=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/09/12/us/12tribes.html?_r=0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2016/11/01/500268879/more-than-a-million-check-in-on-facebook-to-support-the-standing-rock-sioux&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2016/11/01/500268879/more-than-a-million-check-in-on-facebook-to-support-the-standing-rock-sioux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://abcnews.go.com/US/dakota-access-pipeline-protester-felt-betrayed-dog-kennel/story?id=43251043&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://abcnews.go.com/US/dakota-access-pipeline-protester-felt-betrayed-dog-kennel/story?id=43251043&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ocetisakowincamp.org/single-post/2016/11/29/Untitled&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.ocetisakowincamp.org/single-post/2016/11/29/Untitled&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/georgianne-nienaber/fcc-investigates-stingray_b_12680294.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/georgianne-nienaber/fcc-investigates-stingray_b_12680294.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 16:08:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-12-04-fight-for-the-future-stands-with-standing-rock/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-12-04-fight-for-the-future-stands-with-standing-rock/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>URGENT: The FBI, CIA, and other law enforcement agencies get expanded powers to hack into your computer and phone on Thursday, December 1. Some senators are pushing legislation to stop them, but they need more senators to join them immediately.</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning at midnight on Thursday, December 1, 2016, anyone who uses a VPN, Tor browser, or other privacy protection tools can more easily get hacked by the government.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The FBI and other law enforcement agencies are scheduled to get expanded powers to remotely access and search computers, phones, and storage devices in cases where people suspected of being “related” to a crime  use technological means to conceal their location. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is, unless Congress takes action to stop these hacking powers from taking effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under current criminal procedure rules, if the FBI or any other agency wants to hack into your computer, they need to get a warrant from a federal judge located within your federal judicial district. Under a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justsecurity.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/proposed-amendment-rule-41.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;amendment&lt;/a&gt; to the rule that takes effect on Thursday, if you use encryption, disable location tracking, or have been a botnet victim, the FBI can get a warrant to hack you from any of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fedbar.org/PDFs/A-Guide-to-the-Federal-Magistrate-Judge-System.aspx?FT=.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;more than 500&lt;/a&gt; federal magistrate judges around the country. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, if the FBI wants to hack you but they don’t have evidence that passes muster with your local federal judge, they will be able to take their case to a more lenient (or more naïve) judge located anywhere in the country. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another clause in the rule change would let any federal judge authorize hacking operations for multiple devices in cases involving the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act. That means if you are a victim of a botnet or had your computer infected by some malware, the government could remotely hack you under a mass hacking warrant issued by any federal judge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rule change was never voted on—or even debated—by Congress. It comes from the Judicial Conference, the national policy-making body for the federal courts, which earlier in the year agreed to a FBI proposal to amend Rule 41 of the Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure (FRCrmP) so they could get warrants to hack multiple computers in different districts. The Judicial Conference has authority to make technical changes to the rules governing criminal proceedings, but this proposal goes way beyond mere technicalities and should be subject to public and legislative debate.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;We don’t have much time, but we can still stop the government from getting these new mass hacking powers. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.decidethefuture.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dial 1-919-FREEDOM or use this page to get connected with your senators&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bipartisan group of senators and representatives is pushing legislation to block the Judicial Conference’s amendment or at least delay it for a few months so Congress can hold a debate. They will be bringing their bills to the floor for unanimous consent consideration on Tuesday and Wednesday. If no senators object, the bills could pass. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Congress is unlikely to approve the bill to fully block the rule change (the so-called “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.congress.gov/bill/114th-congress/house-bill/5321&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Stop Mass Hacking Act&lt;/a&gt;”) they could possibly be convinced to pass a bill from Senator Chris Coons to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.congress.gov/bill/114th-congress/senate-bill/3475?q=%7B%22search%22%3A%5B%22coons%22%5D%7D&amp;amp;r=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;delay it until July 1, 2017&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to strategists on the Hill, the best approach at this late stage is to get the Senate to pass the bill first and then use that as pressure to urge the House to follow suit &amp;ndash; ideally before the rule change takes effect on Thursday, but they could also pass it at a later date and have the rule change repealed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The best thing you can do to stop the hacking rule is to call your senators and Majority Leader Mitch McConnell to ask them to delay the rule change. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.decidethefuture.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dial 1-919-FREEDOM or use this page to get connected with your senators&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;After you call your senators, make an extra call to Majority Leader McConnell and urge him to agree to unanimous consent on delaying the Rule 41 change. You can reach him at (202) 224-2541.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you should say when you call your senators:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“I am a constituent from [town or city] and I am calling to urge the Senator to agree to unanimous consent on legislation to delay the Rule 41 changes on warrant requirements for government hacking of people’s computers. This rule change could have a big impact on the privacy of all Americans and it should be debated by Congress before going into effect.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find your senators’ numbers below. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Alabama&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeff Sessions  (202) 224-4124&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Shelby  (202) 224-5744&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Alaska&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lisa Murkowski  (202) 224-6665&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daniel Sullivan  (202) 224-3004&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Arizona &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeff Flake  (202) 224-4521&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John McCain  (202) 224-2235&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Arkansas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Boozman  (202) 224-4843&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom Cotton  (202) 224-2353&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;California&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barbara Boxer  (202) 224-3553&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dianne Feinstein  (202) 224-3841&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Colorado&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Bennet  (202) 224-5852&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cory Gardner  (202) 224-5941&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Connecticut&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Blumenthal  (202) 224-2823&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris Murphy  (202) 224-4041&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Delaware&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom Carper  (202) 224-2441&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris Coons  (202) 224-5042&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florida&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bill Nelson  (202) 224-5274&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marco Rubio  (202) 224-3041&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Georgia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Johnny Isakson  (202) 224-3643&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Perdue  (202) 224-3521&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hawaii&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mazie Hirono  (202) 224-6361&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brian Schatz  (202) 224-3934&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Idaho&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Crapo  (202) 224-6142&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Risch  (202) 224-2752&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Illinois&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dick Durbin  (202) 224-2152&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Kirk  (202) 224-2854&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Indiana&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daniel Coats  (202) 224-5623&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joe Donnelly  (202) 224-4814&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Iowa&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joni Ernst  (202) 224-3254&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chuck Grassley  (202) 224-3744&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kansas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jerry Moran  (202) 224-6521&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pat Roberts  (202) 224-4774&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kentucky&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mitch McConnell  (202) 224-2541&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rand Paul  (202) 224-4343&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Louisiana&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bill Cassidy  (202) 224-5824&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Vitter  (202) 224-4623&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Susan Collins  (202) 224-2523&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angus King  (202) 224-5344&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maryland&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben Cardin  (202) 224-4524&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barbara Mikulski  (202) 224-4654&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elizabeth Warren  (202) 224-4543&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ed Markey  (202) 224-2742&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Michigan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gary Peters  (202) 224-6221&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Debbie Stabenow  (202) 224-4822&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Minnesota&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Al Franken  (202) 224-5641&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amy Klobuchar  (202) 224-3244&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mississippi&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger Wicker  (202) 224-6253&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thad Cochran  (202) 224-5054&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Missouri&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roy Blunt  (202) 224-5721&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire McCaskill  (202) 224-6154&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Montana&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve Daines  (202) 224-2651&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jon Tester  (202) 224-2644&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nebraska&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deb Fischer  (202) 224-6551&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben Sasse  (202) 224-4224&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nevada&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harry Reid  (202) 224-3542&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dean Heller  (202) 224-6244&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Hampshire&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelly Ayotte  (202) 224-3324&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jean Shaheen  (202) 224-2841&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Jersey&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cory Booker  (202) 224-3224&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Menendez  (202) 224-4744&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Mexico&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Martin Heinrich  (202) 224-5521&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom Udall  (202) 224-6621&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New York&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kirsten Gillibrand  (202) 224-4451&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chuck Schumer  (202) 224-6542&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;North Carolina&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thom Tillis  (202) 224-6342&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Burr  (202) 224-3154&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;North Dakota&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heidi Heitkamp  (202) 224-2043&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Hoeven  (202) 224-2551&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ohio&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sherrod Brown  (202) 224-2315&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rob Portman  (202) 224-3353&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Oklahoma&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jim Inhofe  (202) 224-4721&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Lankford  (202) 224-5754&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Oregon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeff Merkley  (202) 224-3753&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ron Wyden  (202) 224-5244&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pennsylvania&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bob Casey  (202) 224-6324&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pat Toomey  (202) 224-4254&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rhode Island&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jack Reed  (202) 224-4642&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sheldon Whitehouse  (202) 224-2921&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;South Carolina&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lindsey Graham  (202) 224-5972&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Scott  (202) 224-6121&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;South Dakota&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Rounds  (202) 224-5842&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Thune  (202) 224-2321&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tennessee&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lamar Alexander  (202) 224-4944&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bob Corker  (202) 224-3344&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Texas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Cornyn  (202) 224-2934&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz  (202) 224-5922&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Utah&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Orrin Hatch  (202) 224-5251&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Lee  (202) 224-5444&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Vermont&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pat Leahy  (202) 224-4242&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bernie Sanders  (202) 224-5141&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Virginia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Kaine  (202) 224-4024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Warner  (202) 224-2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Washington&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria Cantwell  (202) 224-3441&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patty Murray (202) 224-2621&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;West Virginia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shelley Moore Capito  (202) 224-6472&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joe Manchin  (202) 224-3954&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wisconsin&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tammy Baldwin  (202) 224-5653&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ron Johnson  (202) 224-5323&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wyoming&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Barrasso  (202) 224-6441&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Enzi  (202) 224-3424&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 10:20:11 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-29-urgent-the-fbi-cia-and-other-law-enforcement/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-29-urgent-the-fbi-cia-and-other-law-enforcement/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning attorneys request commutation of sentence to time served</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Chelsea Manning’s legal defense team released a letter sent to the U.S. Army and the Office of the Pardon Attorney, requesting the commutation of Ms. Manning’s 35 year court-martial sentence to time served and “a first chance to live a real, meaningful life.” The letter discusses the harsh and inhumane conditions Ms. Manning was subjected to in unlawful pretrial solitary confinement for nearly a year.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B9t2hnplz4-aemxBbk1mTVVOQ1U/view&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B9t2hnplz4-aemxBbk1mTVVOQ1U/view&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;View the full letters to the Secretary of the Army and President Obama’s Pardon Attorney here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is helping spread the word about a Whitehouse.gov petition calling for President Obama to reduce Manning’s sentence to time served.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/commute-chelsea-mannings-sentence-time-served-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See the petition here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future is a nonprofit that protects free speech in the digital age. We have been supporting Chelsea Manning while she is incarcerated, and released this letter with the permission of her attorneys.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 15:04:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-14-chelsea-manning-attorneys-request-commutation-of/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-14-chelsea-manning-attorneys-request-commutation-of/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future statement on the death of the Trans-Pacific Partnership: “Donald Trump didn’t kill the TPP, we did.”</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/3b2d5572272d5869ae73bccb405eb90c/tumblr_inline_ogi3572RCT1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;912&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1368&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, November 11, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Unprecedented grassroots uprising made backroom corporate trade deal politically toxic; public overwhelmingly rejects corruption and secrecy&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, media &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wsj.com/articles/obama-administration-gives-up-on-pacific-trade-deal-1478895824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; indicate that the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) is officially dead. &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, a digital rights group best known for organizing some of the largest online protests in history against Internet censorship, for net neutrality, and against government surveillance, along with the celebrity-studded &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; concert tour, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director, Evan Greer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While the world is reeling from the results of the U.S. election, all those who stand on the side of Internet freedom, transparency, and democracy, can take a moment today to celebrate an historic victory: together we stopped the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s make one thing clear: Donald Trump didn’t kill the TPP. We did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unprecedented grassroots movement of people and organizations from across the political spectrum came together to spark an uprising that stopped what would have been nothing less than an outright corporate takeover of our democratic process. Together we sounded the alarm, and made the TPP so politically toxic that no presidential candidate who wanted to be elected could support it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP would have globalized Internet censorship, undermined civil liberties, and devastated our economy and our planet.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unlikely band of labor unions and tech companies, environmentalists, hackers, and Tea Party patriots took on the world’s largest and most powerful corporations, and we won.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we enter a new stage in history, let the movement that stopped the TPP serve as a reminder to the powerful: we are many, and you are few. We will no longer accept blatant political corruption in the form of rigged “trade” deals negotiated in secret. We will fight for the future of free speech and democracy, and in long run, we will always win.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future has been instrumental in the movement against the TPP. They spearheaded the coalition behind &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stopfasttrack.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;StopFastTrack.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; that drove hundreds of thousands of emails and phone calls to Congress in opposition to Trade Promotion Authority legislation needed to pass the TPP, and organized creative stunts like&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDKzwB8GhN0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;b&gt;flying blimps&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; outside of fence-sitting Congress member’s offices. They organized thousands of websites for an online &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/117173257703/thousands-of-websites-protest-fast-track-trade&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;“Internet Vote”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; protest against the TPP, and sent &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/121088291048/photos-video-house-republicans-receive&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;“rubber stamps”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to Republicans who were considering supporting Obama’s trade deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most recently, the group lead the largest ground mobilizations against the TPP to date on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; concert tour, which featured an array of well known musicians and celebrities including Rage Against the Machine guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt;, actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt;, hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli,&lt;/b&gt; comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, and punk legends &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt;, and Jello Biafra of the &lt;b&gt;Dead Kennedys&lt;/b&gt;. The tour drew large crowds across the country and helped opposition to the TPP reach into the cultural mainstream, with high profile media coverage and a large multigenerational following.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for Future is best known for organizing the massive online protests against the SOPA internet censorship bill in 2012, and has since won major victories for net neutrality and against government surveillance. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:17:46 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-11-fight-for-the-future-statement-on-the-death-of-the/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-11-fight-for-the-future-statement-on-the-death-of-the/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS &amp; VIDEO: Hundreds rally at Rock Against the TPP in Pittsburgh</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1399&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;2048&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/ece97ce07c3af2b60d8f08f741b02015/tumblr_inline_og4i5aK5KR1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1399&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;2048&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, November 4, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, (978) 852-6457&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PITTSBURGH, PA––Hundreds packed into Mr Smalls Theater in Pittsburgh last night to protest the anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement at the “Rock Against the TPP” concert headlined by legendary political punk band Anti-Flag. The event was part of a nationwide tour featuring high profile musicians and celebrities raising awareness about controversial deal, which is expected to come up for a vote in Congress during the “lame duck” session after the election.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of the event available for use by press here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/I9RrK&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/I9RrK&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a short VIDEO from the finale of the event here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/p8ngUeInoKw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/p8ngUeInoKw&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The concert also featured renowned Pittsburgh folksinger Anne Feeney along with Downtown Boys, Taina Asili, Ryan Harvey, Son of Nun, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP has little to do with trade, but instead grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to threaten jobs, the environment, affordable medicine, free speech, and food safety. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anti-Flag are one of the most popular musical acts to emerge from Pittsburgh, and tour extensively performing politically charged punk rock that’s half circle pit, half picket line. The band issued the following statement ahead of the November 3rd concert: &amp;ldquo;The Rock Against The TPP shows that we have played across the US and Canada were so amazing that we had to curate one in our beloved hometown of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania - Pittsburgh, an international epicenter of the labor movement  - a city where union loyalty and the fight for human rights courses through the veins of its citizens to this very day. The Rock Against The TPP shows are beyond educational, they&amp;rsquo;re inspirational. They are a true testament to music&amp;rsquo;s ability to bring people together and create positive change; a rally to energize us all to continue to fight against The TPP and all of the ills it will bring to the world.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Trans-Pacific Partnership is not about ‘free trade,’ it’s about corruption,” said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future and lead organizer of the tour, “we’re harnessing the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about this corporate power grab and stop it in its tracks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by digital rights group Fight for the Future in partnership with legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave) and riot-folk singer Ryan Harvey’s record label Firebrand Records, previous stops on the Rock Against the TPP tour have featured high-profile participants including actress Evangeline Lilly, hip hop icon Talib Kweli, comedian Hari Kondabolu, Dead Kennedys singer Jello Biafra, legendary punk band Anti-Flag, Danbert Nobacon of the UK sensation Chumbawamba, and ANTI records songwriter Jolie Holland. The roadshow has already drawn &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;large crowds&lt;/a&gt; in Denver, San Diego, Seattle, Portland, San Francisco, and Toronto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rock Against the TPP tour brings together a broad coalition of supporters including digital rights groups, labor unions, environmental groups, and small businesses, and is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers. The Pittsburgh stop was also backed by the Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, PA Fair Trade Coalition, and Fight Back Pittsburgh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Interviews with artists or organizers, please contact Evan Greer at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or (978) 852-6457.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 11:12:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-04-photos-video-hundreds-rally-at-rock-against-the/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-11-04-photos-video-hundreds-rally-at-rock-against-the/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One year after hitting 100k signatures, Obama still hasn’t responded to the “We the People” petition asking him to support strong encryption.</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;One year ago, the “We the People” &lt;a href=&quot;https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/publicly-affirm-your-support-strong-encryption&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;petition&lt;/a&gt; calling on President Obama to stand for strong encryption reached the 100,000 signature threshold that is supposed to trigger a response from the President. We never heard from him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today—one year later—Fight for the Future and 17 other groups are once again calling on the President to acknowledge and respond to the 100,000+ people that signed this petition. President Obama and the incoming president have a responsibility to 
defend online security for everyone. We need to know where they stand on
 this important issue.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dear President Obama,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On September 29, 2015, Access Now, EFF, and a coalition that grew to nearly 50 organizations and companies initiated a petition using your “We the People” platform. The petition asked you to “[p]ublicly affirm your support for strong encryption,” and to “[r]eject any law, policy, or mandate that would undermine our security” online. It also asked you to encourage other governments worldwide  to do the same. The petition, also available at SaveCrypto.org, garnered more than 100,000 signatures in fewer than 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the blog post announcing the creation of We The People, “if a petition gathers enough online signatures, it will be reviewed by policy experts and you’ll receive an official response.” At the time our petition was submitted the threshold for official response was (and currently is) 100,000 signatures within 30 days. Further, the website pledges an official response within 60 days of meeting that threshold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has been 365 days — a full year — since our petition exceeded 100,000 signatures, and while in December 2015 your administration created an online portal for signatories to offer more information, there has still been no substantive response. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Encryption tools enable journalists, whistleblowers, organizers, and regular people to communicate securely. It assures users of the integrity of their data and authenticates individuals to companies, governments, and one another. Further, the ability to confidently communicate and conduct business online is a necessary foundation of economic growth in the digital age. The United Nations Special Rapporteur for freedom of expression recently noted, “[e]ncryption and anonymity, separately or together, create a zone of privacy to protect opinion and belief.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the 365 days since our petition hit the 100,000 signatory threshold to ensure a response from the administration, the FBI attempted to force Apple to build an entirely new, insecure operating system to bypass its security protocols and the U.S. Congress and legislatures in individual states have debated passing harmful anti-security legislation that would endanger the technology sector globally. Around the world, governments have capitalized on the lack of leadership in support for encryption and implemented harmful laws and policies. China specifically cited to the rhetoric in the U.S. last December when it passed a new law that likely bans end to end encryption, with no upper limit on fines for non-compliant companies. The UK is on the cusp of passing a law that could, practically, have the same impact. And from Brazil to Russia to India we are seeing other actions or proposals that could undermine the security of the global internet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. President, your response is urgently needed to clarify the United States’ position and establish its leadership on this critically important topic. The United States should once and for all repudiate any type of mandate requiring third-party access to encrypted data, both stored and in transit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leading candidates for president have commented on the importance of strengthening U.S. cybersecurity. A cornerstone to those plans must be an increase in the development and use of strong encryption. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access Now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocacy for Principled Action in Government&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American Library Association&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amnesty International&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Center for Media Justice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumer Technology Association (CTA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Constitutional Alliance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Electronic Frontier Foundation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free Press&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freedom of the Press Foundation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight For the Future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global Network Initiative&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights Watch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New America&amp;rsquo;s Open Technology Institute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Niskanen Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OpenTheGovernment.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Restore the Fourth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;World Privacy Forum&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 10:07:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-27-one-year-after-hitting-100k-signatures-obama/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-27-one-year-after-hitting-100k-signatures-obama/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>For-Profit AT&amp;T Spying Program is Worse Than Snowden Revelations</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future statement in response to report detailing AT&amp;amp;T’s massive secret surveillance program, paid for with taxpayer money&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, it was &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2016/10/25/at-t-is-spying-on-americans-for-profit.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;revealed&lt;/a&gt; that AT&amp;amp;T has been running a massive secret spying program—funded by tens of millions in taxpayer money—for state and local law enforcement agencies to conduct warrantless searches of trillions of call records and other extremely sensitive customer data such as precise physical location. &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, a digital rights group known for its high profile campaigns for free speech and online security, released the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director, Evan Greer:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The for-profit spying program that these documents detail is more terrifying than the illegal NSA surveillance programs that Edward Snowden exposed. Far beyond the NSA and FBI, these tools are accessible to a wide range of law enforcement officers including local police, without a warrant, as long as they pay up. It makes me sick to my stomach thinking about it. Customers trusted AT&amp;amp;T with some of their most private information, and the company turned around and literally built a product to sell that information to as many government agencies and police departments as they could. Not only did they fail to have any safeguards to prevent unauthorized use of the data, they actually required law enforcement to keep the program secret and dig up or fabricate other evidence, to hide the fact that they’d received information from AT&amp;amp;T. If companies are allowed to operate in this manner without repercussions, our democracy has no future. We call on AT&amp;amp;T to immediately shut down this illegal and unethical spying program, and we demand that the U.S. department of Justice launch an investigation into the use of the Hemisphere spying program, and reveal all court cases where Hemisphere was used so that they can be reviewed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is best known for organizing some of the largest online protests in history including the massive SOPA Blackout, the Internet Slowdown for net neutrality, and Reset the Net opposing mass government surveillance. Learn more at FightForTheFuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 15:00:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-25-for-profit-att-spying-program-is-worse-than/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-10-25-for-profit-att-spying-program-is-worse-than/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

